印度是伟大的！
lndia is great!
属于不同宗教的人一起生活在这里和平。
People belonging to different religions are living together peacefully here.
这就是为什么，印度是伟大的！
That's why, lndia is great!
敌国，恐怖分子，黑手党试图以多种方式破坏我们的团结，
Enemy states, terrorists, mafia tried in many ways to break our unity,
他们还在试图，
they're still trying,
一个这样的尝试是1993年孟买爆炸，
one such attempt is 1993 Mumbai blasts,
1998年哥印拜陀炸弹爆炸事件，攻击2002 Akshardam，
1998 Coimbatore bomb blasts, 2002 Akshardam attacks,
2007年，2013年海得拉巴的爆炸事件，
2007, 2013 Hyderabad blasts,
他们试图打破我们除了用许多这样的令人发指的行为，
they tried to break us apart with many such heinous acts,
但他们甚至不能采摘头发，
but they couldn't even pluck a hair strand,
这就是精神印度，
that's the spirit of lndia,
孟买爆炸事件后，许多歹徒跑开从印度，
After Mumbai blasts, many gangsters ran away from lndia,
其中之一是苦行僧BHAI的，
one among them is Sadhu Bhai,
后征服新加坡，香港，马来西亚，菲律宾，
after conquering Singapore, Hong Kong, Malaysia, Philippines,
他成为东南亚黑手党教父，
he became Godfather to South East Asian mafia,
联手恐怖的服装，
joining forces with terrorist outfits,
乱军与死亡和炸弹爆炸，
creating chaos with death and bomb blasts,
苦行僧BHAI印度n政府已经成为一个大问题，
Sadhu bhai who had become a big problem to lndian Government,
没有人敢阻止他20年，
no one could dare stop him for 20 years,
第一人挑战苦行僧BHAI的是Baadshah - 在香港举行...
the first man to challenge Sadhu bhai is Baadshah!- A place in Hong Kong...
任何人谁进入黑手党生计，或恐吓他人，
Anyone who enters mafia for livelihood or to terrorise others,
但Baadshah已经进入黑手党的世界为他的父亲，
but Baadshah has entered mafia world for his father,
Baadshah，你已经动摇了世界的黑手党。
Baadshah, you've shaken the world of mafia.
但犯了许多错误。
But committed many mistakes.
你敢采取苦行僧BHAI的黑手党教父，
You've dared to taken on Sadhu bhai, Godfather of mafia,
你杀了我的兄弟，
you killed my brother,
关于电影，我狂升手表每天两部电影，
l'm mad about films, l watch two films every day,
每次看升升得到一个疑问，
Every time l watched l used to get a doubt,
如果一个人的被捕而不是杀死他，为什么他们给他讲课？
if a man's caught instead of killing him, why do they lecture to him?
现在，我是清楚。
Now l'm clear.
我已经经历了它一脚。 得到它。
l've experienced the kick in it. l got it.
L'没有立刻杀了你。
l'm not killing you immediately.
L'VE给你更多的痛苦。 怎么样？
l've to give you more pain. How?
父亲！
Father!
我会杀了你的父亲在你的眼前。
l'll kill your father right before your eyes.
获取Baadshah的父亲！
Get Baadshah's father!
lftiger是在细胞内，即使孩子们可以用它玩。
lftiger is inside the cell, even kids can play with it.
当它出来，它开始进入竞技场打猎！
When it comes out into the arena, it begins to hunt!
停止lmpossible。
lmpossible to stop it.
不止是香港警方，印度n警方还找你。
Notjust the police of Hong Kong, lndian police is also searching for you.
好好照顾我的父亲，
Take good care of my father,
每一个问题有一个解决方案，
there's a solution to every problem,
我发现解决方案，它可能是任何地方。
l'll find that solution wherever it may be.
几天后... 米兰，ltaly ...
Few days later... Milan, ltaly...
一个人希望他的安全，养了一只狗，
One who wants his security rears a dog,
希望社会安全种植的树木！
one who wants society to be secure grows trees!
现在，我获得的权利，有早餐。
Now l've earned the right to have breakfast.
来吧早餐。 - 你知道该怎么告诉她，对不对？
Come for breakfast. - You know what to tell her, right?
今日早盘升打扫厕所，姐姐。
Today morning l cleaned the toilet, sister.
我喷粉，姐姐。 - 我知道你们俩什么也没做。
l did the dusting, sister. - l know you both didn't do anything.
首先吃早餐。
Have breakfast first.
您承担，我们说做了一些很好的赢得权利，有早餐，
You bore us saying got to do some good to earn the right to have breakfast,
怎么来的，你提供早餐，没有任何演讲，姐姐？
how come you're offering breakfast without any lecture, sister?
没什么，我已经完成了我的室内设计课程，
Nothing, l've finished my interior designing course here,
我是回去到印度，
l'm going back to lndia,
所以我想这最后的10天难忘和享受它的剑柄。
so l want these last 10 days memorable and enjoy it to the hilt.
你要带我们，姐姐？ - 有没有踢，如果告诉你。
Where are you taking us, sister? - There's no kick if l tell you.
这实在是太多了，姐姐。 我们在这里，因为我们的童年，
This is too much, sister. We're here since our childhood,
甚至邻居不知道我们的名字，
even neighbours don't know our names,
但你在短短的一年成为名人。
but you've become a celebrity in just a year.
像索尼娅离开意大利定居印度，姐姐会离开印度，在这里定居。
Like Sonia left ltaly to settle in lndia, sister will leave lndia to settle here.
你困惑了这么多问候她？
Are you confused about so many greeting her?
LT的打招呼的义大利语。
lt's hello in ltalian language.
要知道她的追随者，你需要跟随她一段时间。
To know about her followers, you need to follow her for some time.
为什么你给我们带来的医院有望享受，妹妹？
Why did you bring us to hospital promising to enjoy, sister?
你为什么越来越急？
Why are you getting anxious?
你有没有为我们提供早餐献血？
Did you offer us breakfast to donate blood?
我们将不捐。
We'll not donate.
自私是像雪水！ 进入它为您提供了疥疮！
Selfishness is like slush! Get into it gives you scabies!
帮助就像是球，玩给你幸福。
Help is like ball, playing with it gives you happiness.
我们不希望任何幸福。
We don't want any happiness.
你为什么叫我在这里迫切？ 每个人都很好，对不对？
Why did you call me here urgently? Everyone is fine, right?
我们没事，你就会失去现在血。 - 再次献血？
We're fine, you'll lose blood now. - Blood donation again?
你知道它是多么困难，统筹用于电影拍摄。
You know how difficult it is to co-ordinate for film shoots.
Balaiah位置！
Balaiah is on location!
叔叔，你赚钱的协调电影拍摄，
Uncle, your earn money coordinating film shoots,
献血会为您的生活添加善行。
blood donation would add good deeds to your life.
这就是如果我们一旦在6个月内，每个月会给我的弱点。
That's ifwe do once in 6 months, every month would give me weakness.
他们会给你吃的苹果。
They'll give you apple to eat.
你不用担心，叔叔。 我们就住在这里。
You don't worry, uncle. We'll stay here only.
他们把一升血，给了这个苹果。
They took a litre blood and gave this apple.
他们吸B阳性。
They sucked B positive only.
叔叔，好事是打在墙上的像一个球，
Uncle, good deed is like a ball hit on the wall,
你做的好，你会得到很好的回报。
you do good, you get good in return.
信任你的球，
Trusting your ball,
上个月，L接受信贷生产者，
last month, l accepted credit for a producer,
他没有回答我的电话，
he's not answering my phone calls,
现在一天的善良是不是在墙壁上投中一球，
now a day's goodness isn't a ball hit on the wall,
它的粉饰OFTHE墙，
it's whitewash ofthe wall,
如果你从头开始，它会伤害你的指甲！
ifyou scratch, it'll hurt your nails!
叔叔被伤害！
Uncle is hurt!
LS呢？ 谢谢你！
ls it? Thank you!
发生了什么事，叔叔？
What happened, uncle?
它似乎生产者已支付的钱。
lt seems that producer has paid the money.
你说什么？ - 你的球已经赢了。
What do you say now? - Your ball has won.
从你父亲学习。
Learn from your father.
你分享他的血，但不是他的善良。
You shared his blood but not his goodness.
他们的血型是不同的，对不对？ 他们没有像我这样的大心脏 - 叔叔！
Their blood group is different, right? They don't have a big heart like me.- Uncle!
它给我们的危险，我们什么都可以说！
lt's danger to us what ever we may say!
她会记住的东西。
She'll remember something.
心，使我想起今天是世界心脏日！
Heart makes me remember today is World Heart Day!
l必须马上去儿童心脏保健。
l must immediately go to child heart care.
对不起，亲爱的，吝啬的上帝给了我只有一个心脏。
Sorry dear, stingy God gave me only one heart.
叔叔？
Uncle?
我们不能这样做了，姐姐。
We can't do it anymore, sister.
我们正在做的学士学位和乞讨的乞丐一样，这是什么？
We're doing bachelor's degree and begging like beggars, what's this?
lfyou帮助别人，看着他们的眼睛......
lfyou help someone and look into their eyes...
他们会怀疑你色迷迷地盯着他们！
They'll suspect you're ogling at them!
l可以不改革！ 计数的集合。
l can't reform you! Count the collection.
LS捐款箱Tirupathi算悠闲？
ls it donation box of Tirupathi to count leisurely?
它可能只是5欧元。 让我们去。
lt could be just 5 Euros. Let's go.
我的目标是10000欧元，L不会移动，直到升实现它。
My target is 10000 Euros, l won't move till l achieve it.
10000欧元？
10000 Euros?
我们去抢银行。
We've to rob a bank.
不需要，社会良知的人...
No need, people with social conscience...
那是什么？ 社会良知？
What's that? Social conscience...?
我们需要理解你的语言的字典。
We need dictionary to understand your language.
迈克尔・杰克逊一定要来这里，来实现你的目标。
Michael Jackson must come here to achieve your target.
我不记得那是6月或7月，倒升爱上了她......
l don't remember it was June or July, l fell in love with her...
罗密欧我，一个孤独的情人，我的爱是不是跟我现在...
l'm a Romeo, a lonely lover, my love isn't with me now...
我是传播以无限的爱在我有限的心脏...
l'm spread an unlimited love within my limited heart...
你是我的心脏，灵魂和生命...
You're my heart, soul and life...
我是疯狂地寻找华阳秋刀鱼，你是我唯一的幸福的生活......
l'm frantically searching foryou Saira, you're my only happiness in life...
冬季热浪是因为ofyou的...
Heat waves in winter is because ofyou...
我没有你什么？
What am l without you?
我航空火力达到你的河流......
l've to rivers offire to reach you...
L'VE一颗勇敢的心，为什么会这样婉转？
l've a brave heart, why is it so mellowed?
我来无论你是在不断的方向......
l'll come wherever you are in which ever direction...
您好！ - 为什么你的行为像一个傻瓜，秋刀鱼？
Hello!- Why are you behaving like a fool, Saira?
你知道我为你像个疯子一样在街上跳舞？
Do you know l'm dancing on streets like a mad man for you?
但你还是没有打开，你为什么用我的生命打球吗？
But still you didn't turn up, why are you playing ball with my life?
你所做的一切，那个女孩，当她来到谢谢，
You did everything for that girl, when she came to thank you,
你为什么要避开她？
why did you avoid her?
关系会得到削减在这里感谢，
Relationship would get cut here with thanks,
现在升回避她，她会认为我今晚！
now that l avoided her, she would think about me tonight!
他帮助和消失了！
He helped and vanished!
请确保升再次见到他... - 我永远不会再看到！
Please ensure l see him again... - l'll never be seen again!
您也想，秋刀鱼？
You too wish that, right Saira?
您没有我会很高兴的，对不对？
You'd be happy without me, right?
这就是为什么，不止是从你的生活中，我是离开这个世界的好。
That's why, notjust from your life, l'm leaving this world for good.
嘿，小子，你！
Hey boy, you!
我未来，呆在那里！
l'm coming, stay there!
不要动，你可能会死！
Don't move, you may die!
为什么你要到死这么年轻？ - 不要来了，你也想死吗？
Why do you want to die so young? - Don't come, do you also want to die?
来......来升说！
Come...come l say!
你为什么阻止我？
Why are you stopping me?
你帮了不少忙，在您不知情的情况下，为慈善筹款。
You helped a lot without your knowledge to raise funds for charity.
然后，帮我推我下来。
Then, help me by pushing me down.
什么废话？ 我花了一天。
What's that nonsense? Spend a day with me.
我是不是该类型。
l'm not that type.
L'不便宜。 - 不惜血本？
l'm not that cheap. - Costly?
我是不是那种类型！
l'm not that type at all!
但是你问我花了一天的你，对吧？
But you asked me to spend a day with you, right?
花了我一天，我给一百个理由住，
Spend a day with me l'll give hundred reasons to live,
并证明生活是美好的。
and prove that life is beautiful.
请听我说一次。
Please listen to me once.
你阻止我的挫折比我死的挫折是比较危险的。
Your frustration to stop me is more dangerous than my frustration to die.
谢谢你，你得到了它。
Thanks, you got it.
一般来说，一个垂死的人询问最后的愿望，
Generally, a dying person asks for last wish,
但你问一个垂死的人。
but you're asking for a dying man.
所以我是给你一天！
So l'm giving you a day!
那是什么？
What's that?
如果升不上生活，你必须删除我这里，明天得到任何希望。
lf l don't get any hope on life, you must drop me here tomorrow.
因为我没有钱乘出租车也。
Because l don't have money for taxi also.
听到这个名字Peter甚上，它有着悠久的倒叙故事。
On hearing this name Peter Ganesh, it has a long flashback story.
我们需要耐心想听吗？
Do we need patience to hear it?
你拦住我从死亡的，为什么要麻烦我与彼得甚？
You stopped me from dying and why trouble me with Peter Ganesh?
拉玛饶，L'米的点，不要沮丧。
Don't get frustrated Rama Rao, l'm coming to the point.
彼得太像你试图自杀。
Peter too tried to commit suicide like you.
我救了他，因为在那里。
l could save him because l was there.
升带他回家问，什么是你的问题，彼得？
l took him to home and asked, what's your problem, Peter?
他告诉我。
He told me.
他破产了，做不同种类的业务。
He went bankrupt doing different kinds of business.
可能做一个业务蓬勃发展。
May have prospered doing one business.
他的合伙人欺骗了他。 - 你的意思是像我的秋刀鱼巴努。
His partners cheated him. - You mean like my Saira Banu.
我告诉他，你死的勇气，为什么不尝试与它生活呢？
l told him you've courage to die, why not try living with it?
他掉进线只用一个坐姿。
He fell into line with just one sitting.
升观察到，在他的家乡，食物非常可口，
l observed that food is very tasty in his home,
升建议开一家餐馆，并提出了他主Ganesh神的偶像。
l suggested opening a restaurant and presented him idol of Lord Ganesh.
其实升了他的信仰不是一个偶像。
Actually l gave him faith not an idol.
企业成功有信心和削弱了他的问题。
Business succeeded with faith and his problem weakened.
他意识到这点。 您了解什么？
He realised that. What did you understand from this?
不要扔掉球得到施舍，不要毁了生活困难。
Never throw away ball got as alms, don't ruin life for difficulties.
像补球，使其工作，生活和修补矣。
Like mending ball to make it work, patch up life and carry on.
煤矿是不是财务问题，如彼得使其工作补丁。
Mine isn't financial problem like Peter to make it work with patches.
得到它。
l got it.
像彼得一坐，每个人都会被说服。
Everyone won't get convinced with one sitting like Peter.
你需要更多的开庭。
You need more sittings.
L了解应该从这个雕像是什么？ - 耐心等待！
What should l learn from this statue? - Patience!
詹姆斯是一个臭名昭著的回升口袋。
James was a notorious pick-pocket.
观察他的天赋你是什么？
What was the talent you observed in him?
他可以像豺等待几个小时，挑别人的口袋里。
He can wait for hours like a jackal to pick someone's pocket.
我抓住它，你希望他能兑现这样的。
l got it, you wanted him to cash it like this.
詹姆斯用扒手较早，但人们现在自愿给钱。
James used to pick pockets earlier but people are giving money voluntarily now.
妹妹！ - 得到了他吗？
Hi sister! - Got him?
得到他吗？ 如果升上没有达成时间，他就已经一去不复返了。
Got him? Had l not reached on time, he would've gone forever.
他的名字是拉玛饶。 - LS theirfather驴？
His name is Rama Rao. - ls theirfather donkey?
不要难过，他的沮丧，他的爱人欺骗了他。
Don't feel bad, he's frustrated, his lover cheated him.
他看上去像一个骗子。
He appears like a cheat.
看，一个女人骗任何人，谁得到便宜给大家。
See, any man who got cheated by a woman is cheap to everyone.
我来到异国他乡秋刀鱼巴努
l came to a foreign country for Saira Banu,
在我的口袋里没有一分钱，
not a penny in my pocket,
每当升想想她的欺骗，
whenever l think about her cheating,
我真希望有人抱着我不放，
l wish someone hugs me tightly,
并说拉玛饶，不要担心我有华阳，
and say Rama Rao, don't worry l'm there foryou,
但谁是在这里为我？ 没有！ 离开我，我会走开。
but who is here for me? None! Leave me, l'll go away.
拉玛饶，停止！ - 离开我，我会死的。
Rama Rao, stop! - Leave me, l'll die.
不要担心，我会在你身边。
Don't worry, l'm there for you.
他让她拥抱他。
He made her hug him.
秋刀鱼巴努为什么踢足球与我的生活吗？
Why is Saira Banu playing football with my life?
足球带给我的记忆中，
Football brings to my memory,
生活就像是一场足球比赛，
life is like a football game,
我们会停止播放游戏ifwe错过球？
would we stop playing game ifwe miss the ball?
我们买一个新球。
We buy a new ball.
lfyou秋刀鱼巴努女士，你可能会得到：Udaya巴努。
lfyou miss Saira Banu, you may get Udaya Banu.
你有什么问题呢？
What's your problem anyway?
这只是板球的大小。
lt's just the size of cricket ball.
l必须告诉你一个战士谁打篮球大小的问题。
l must tell you about a warrior who fought with basket ball sized problems.
谁甩了他？ - 上帝把他甩了！
Who dumped him? - God dumped him!
他失去了母亲，失去了他的父亲在13。
He lost his mother at 3, lost his father at 13.
在23下一页检票？
Next wicket at 23?
没有那么长的差距，他失去了谁提出他明年的姑姑和叔叔。
Not so long gap, he lost aunt and uncle who raised him the next year.
哦，我的上帝！ LS，他还活着后杀死这么多人？
Oh my God! ls he still alive after killing so many people?
这是谁的吃人？
Who is this man eater?
升山的尖端去扔掉啤酒瓶，
l went to the tip of mountain to throw away beer bottle,
那傻丫头以为我是自杀，并带我去她家。
that silly girl thought l was committing suicide and took me to her home.
我不介意失去myjob！ 但生活是很幸福的！
l don't mind losing myjob! But life is very happy!
你会不会这辈子第二次！
You'll not get this life second time!
我给你打电话。
l'll call you later.
你的灵感，
With your inspiration,
希望死去的已经变成了生活的希望，夫人。
wish to die has turned into hope to live, madam.
我已经开发了帮助别人像你这样的态度。
l've developed the attitude of helping others like you.
为你做了什么？
What have you done for that?
升去教堂捐赠面食可怜的孩子，夫人。
l went to a church and donated pasta to poor children, madam.
捐赠面食？
Donated pasta?
LT捐赠大米印度，在这里它捐赠面食。
lt is donating rice in lndia and here it is donating pasta.
下一步呢？ - 升持有隔壁阿姨，夫人。
Next? - l held next door aunty, madam.
升不意味着举行，L拉着她，而她倒下。
l didn't mean that held, l held her while she was falling down.
我的脚！
My foot!
她悄悄走了香蕉皮和l举行了她。
She slipped walking on a banana peel and l held her.
第二章开始在你的自传，夫人，
Started the second chapter in your autobiography, madam,
刚才开始的世界球，它的到来，非常漂亮！
just now started the world of ball, it's coming out very nicely!
我不喜欢这个！ 反正你的愿望。
l don't like this! Anyway as you wish.
球像动物世界这是什么世界？
What's this world of ball like animal world?
难道你不知道有关夫人的球理念？
Don't you know about madam's ball philosophy?
他是谁，夫人？
Who is he, madam?
他拉马饶。 - 他为什么会在这里？
He's Rama Rao. - Why is he here?
他想自杀。 他的爱人，把他甩了。
He wanted to kill himself. His lover dumped him.
发生了什么事？ - 升想起秋刀鱼巴努。
What happened? - l remembered Saira Banu.
我会去......离开我...... - 停止...停...听我说。
l'll go...leave me... - Stop...stop...listen to me.
这是常见的。 - 我的感觉像死亡。
This is common. - l feel like dying.
我真希望把我的下一个正在运行的列车。
l wish to put my under a running train.
什么废话？ 我有华阳。
What's that nonsense? l'm there foryou.
离开他，让他死。 困扰我们的是什么？
Leave him, let him die. What bothers us?
LF我想这样，你会在这里呢？
lf l had thought like that, would you be here now?
他今晚留在这里。 要小心。
He'll stay here tonight. Be careful.
他做任何事情给我吗？ - 见他不伤害自己。
Would he do anything to me? - See that he doesn't harm himself.
告诉男孩我的理念和报价，
Tell the boy about my philosophy and quotations,
并给了他生活的希望。 明白了吗？
and give him a hope in life. Got it?
LF我真的告诉??他，他肯定会死。
lf l really tell him, he'll die for sure.
看拉马饶，
Look Rama Rao,
我们用铅笔写在学校，你知道为什么吗？
we write with pencils in school, do you know why?
lfwe写的错误，我们可以擦，写的是正确的，
lfwe write it wrong, we can rub and write it correctly,
但是当我们长大了，我们得到的笔写，
but when we grow up, we get pens to write,
有没有纠正的机会。
there's no chance of correcting it.
我把这种铅笔理念，在您的传记。
l'll incorporate this pencil philosophy in your biography.
达苏，你知道我不喜欢这一切，对吗？
Dasu, you know l don't like all this, right?
无论如何，你的愿望。
Anyway, as you wish.
今晚认为我说的是什么！ - 关于铅笔，对不对？
Think over tonight what l said! - About pencil, right?
让我们相约明天早上。
Let's meet tomorrow morning.
如果l记得秋刀鱼巴努的平均时间？
What if l remember Saira Banu in the mean time?
你照顾他，达苏。 再见。
You take care of him, Dasu. Bye.
你是从哪个地方？ 你自杀呢？
Which place are you from? Were you committing suicide?
来吧，现在就做，让我看看！
Come on do it now, let me see!
你欺骗她，因为她太天真了？
Are you fooling her because she too innocent?
我撕裂了你的皮！
l'll rip out your skin!
伏特加酒在哪里？ - 伏特加？
Where's the vodka? - Vodka?
味道！ 你能告诉品牌与嗅觉？
Smell! can you tell the brand with smell?
l可以告诉字符，看着眼睛。
l can tell character by looking at eyes.
LS你的家人死了吗？ - 没有人已经死了。 什么都没有！
ls your family dead? - Nobody is dead. Nothing!
你在这里萨拉萨民生，我是在这里。
You're here for livelihood and l'm here for Janaki.
从现在起...... - 我为您服务！
From now onwards... - l'm at your service!
看饶拉玛，一面有死亡和生命的另一边是。
Look Rama Rao, one side there's death and life is on the other side.
决定是在你的手中。
Decision is in your hands.
报价是了不起的！ 我会在你的生平添加。
Quotation is marvelous! l'll add it in your biography.
闭嘴！ 你知道我讨厌这一切！ 反正也如你所愿！
Shut up! You know l hate all this! Anyway do as you wish!
你看，问题是像一个球，
Look, problem is like a ball,
如果你看看它关闭你的眼睛，它会出现大，
ifyou look at it close to your eyes, it'll appear big,
如果你把它扔掉，它似乎非常小。
ifyou throw it away, it appears very small.
我们可以抛出一个球，但怎么能扔秋刀鱼巴努？
We can throw a ball away but how can l throw Saira Banu?
她像一只公牛是巨大的！ - 我了你。
She's huge like a bullock! - l got you.
秋刀鱼巴努你不是不爱而是仇恨！
What you've on Saira Banu isn't love but hatred!
一旦仇恨，你的问题就解决了??。
Once the hatred is out, your problem is solved.
如何才能消除仇恨像去除空气从球？
How can l remove hatred like removing air from a ball?
有一个解决方案，即得。 达苏，来到这里。
There's a solution for that too. Dasu, come here.
认为他是秋刀鱼巴努，扔了，无论是在你的心里。
Think he's Saira Banu, throw up whatever is in your heart.
他有一个沉重的早餐，你问他扔了我呢？
He had a heavy breakfast, are you asking him to throw up on me?
闭上眼睛，深吸一口气！
Close your eyes and take a deep breath!
你吗？ 记住所有巴努秋刀鱼你所犯的暴行！
Did you take? Remember all the atrocities Saira Banu committed on you!
那就是......就是这样......
That is...that's it...
现在打开！
Open up now!
嘿，你，秋刀鱼巴努！
Hey you, Saira Banu!
你怎么折磨我吗？
How you tortured me?
你会使用我像一个仆人，而不考虑我和你？
Will you use me like a servant without considering me as yours?
lfyou变化宿舍，每6个月，应升带你的行李和行李？
lfyou change hostel every 6 months, should l carry you baggage and luggage?
叔叔lfyour拥有一个眼科手术，应升给他带来的食物？
lfyour uncle has an eye operation, should l bring him food?
你坚持给我后，才做了这么多？
Did you stick to me only after doing so much?
多少个男朋友，你像无线电兄弟？
How many boyfriends do you've like radio brothers?
你会爱上你遇到的每一个男人？
Will you fall for every man you meet?
请你给她的电话号码？
Will you please give her phone number?
给我你的电话。
Give me your phone.
你们不觉得丢人保持升给你买手机的朋友吗？
Aren't you ashamed to maintain friends with cell phone l bought for you?
这是什么，夫人？ 这太好了！
What's this, madam? lt's wonderful!
愤怒是我的系统！ - 我的手机也不见了。
Anger is off my system! - My phone too is gone.
顺其自然吧，血腥的手机！
Let it go, bloody phone!
拉玛饶的愤怒已经走了，这很重要。
Rama Rao's anger has gone, that's important.
升失去了死亡的思想在短短的一天，
l lost the thought of dying in just one day,
ifyou给我10天，我会找到一种方式来生活。
ifyou give me 10 days, l'll find a way to live.
姐姐是不是免费的，她回去到印度。
Sister isn't free, she's going back to lndia.
拉玛饶将和我们呆在一起，直到升回去印度的 - 姐姐？
Rama Rao will stay with us till l go back to lndia.- Sister?
你想要一个球可打，他想住一球。
You want a ball to play and he wants a ball to live.
你赶上了所有的球，完全像一个检票口的门将。
You're catching all the balls perfectly like a wicket keeper.
faryourjob如何已达Baadshah？
How faryourjob has reached, Baadshah?
我会见了萨拉萨，我会在不久的将来完成这项工作。
l've met Janaki, l'll accomplish the job in near future.
的信息，在意大利为您苦行僧BHAI的男人。
There's information that Sadhu Bhai's men are in ltaly for you.
照顾爸爸。
Take care of dad.
你为什么反应如此激烈？
Why did you react so violently?
我的反应是，如果有人触动暴力从后面？
My reaction would be violent if anyone touches from behind?
欢迎符合星级程序！
Welcome to meet the star program!
今天，我们的名人，著名电影导演，
Today our celebrity is, famous film director,
“友谊与鬼”，“杀LS我的业余爱好”
'Friendship with Ghost' 'Killing ls My Hobby'
“夜公升血”，“血口渴的人”下雨，
'The Night lt Rained Blood' 'Blood-Thirsty Man',
'骷髅'L'足球就杀了切喉'
'Football with Skull' 'l'll Kill by Cutting Throat'
谁造就了如此可怕和恐怖电影的人，
the man who created such gruesome and terror films,
面对面的程序与'复仇'Nageshwara饶。
a face to face program with 'Revenge' Nageshwara Rao.
的问候。
Greetings.
普瑞Jagannadh去到芭堤雅的故事开庭，
Puri Jagannadh goes to Pattaya for story sittings,
Rajamouli拉贾斯坦邦，你去哪里？
Rajamouli goes to Rajasthan, where do you go?
Cherlapalli监狱！
Cherlapalli jail!
我的故事开庭的罪犯。
My story sittings are with criminals.
董事坐在一起的故事作家，为什么罪犯？
Directors sit with story writers, why criminals?
升不同步以及与作家，犯罪分子完全与我同步。
l don't sync well with writers, criminals sync perfectly with me.
它似乎是你在事务中运行与每个女主角新书膜，是真的吗？
lt seems you run affairs with every heroine ofyour film, is it true?
我们之间offthe屏幕lfthe化学工??程，
lfthe chemistry between us offthe screen works out well,
然后屏幕上的男女主人公之间的化学反应将工作搞好。
only then chemistry between hero and heroine on screen will work out well.
他们说导演是的队长OFTHE船舶，你说什么？
They say director is the captain ofthe ship, what do you say?
升说，它的垃圾！
l say its trash!
在我看来总监不是队长船或驱动OFTHE的出租车，
ln my opinion director isn't captain of ship or driver ofthe taxi,
或海盗OFTHE的平面或所有者OFTHE酒店？
or pirate ofthe plane or owner ofthe wine shop?
然后呢？ - 小偷 - 小偷？
Then? - Thief!- Thief?
àthiefwho将窃取心中票房集合的人民和金钱。
A thiefwho will steal hearts of people and money with box office collections.
新的想法！
New idea!
他们说，在你的电影“刀如血”中的反派是基于现实生活中唐'疯狂'罗伯特。
They say villain in your film 'Knife-Blood' is based on real life Don 'Crazy' Robert.
LS是真的吗？
ls it true?
瞧瞧吧！
Look at that!
无论你在他的片约...
Whatever you had shown in the film about him...
“疯狂”罗伯特是一个可怕的唐大家，
'Crazy' Robert is a fearful Don to you all,
但我的研究结果说，他是一个有趣的家伙。
but result of my research says he's a funny fellow.
一个经纪人，一个小丑，一个浪子，一个主力位置，
A broker, a joker, a loafer, a duffer,
他开始了他的职业生涯作为一个老masseurfor妇女，
he started his career as a masseurfor old women,
当不好的时候把他的老板的收费，
when bad time took the toll of his boss,
幸运的是，他的时间转好，他结束了作为一个唐。
luckily his time turned good and he ended up as a Don.
难道你没有收到任何恐吓电话，从他身上吗？
Didn't you get any threatening calls from him?
有一次，当他打来电话，问Rs.4亿卢比，L说我会踢他。
Once when he called and asked Rs.4 crores, l said l'll kick him.
我告诉他，如果他想致电Ramgopal瓦玛。
l told him to call Ramgopal Varma if he wants.
他吓坏了，并挂断了电话。
He got scared and hang up the phone.
你的下一部电影是什么，先生？
What's your next film, sir?
第一部分以失败告终，以吗？ - 这就是为什么我米两部分。
Part one flopped, right sir? - That's why l'm making part two.
lfthis也无人问津？ - 我会三部分。
lfthis too flops? - l'll make part three.
所以，你想报仇的观众，对不对？
So you want to take revenge on audience, right?
这就是'复仇'Nageshwara饶你！
That's 'Revenge' Nageshwara Rao for you!
网速慢??我的答案感到震惊。
Suman was shocked with my answers.
他用我的手机拨打电话。 - 手机给你的导演。
He's using my phone to make calls. - Give the phone to your director.
好的，先生。
Okay sir.
LT的你，没有人会感到震惊网速慢。
lt's you who would get shocked not Suman.
“疯狂”罗伯特的电话，告诉你是不是在这里吗？
"Crazy' Robert's phone, shall l tell you're not here?
它是什么，罗伯特的男孩？
What's it, Robert boy?
你为什么信口雌黄胡说八道？ 我会子弹泵放进嘴里。
Why are you blabbering nonsense? l'll pump bullets into your mouth.
L'要去ltaly在2天，
l'm going to ltaly in 2 days,
胆量ifyou've，如果你的枪有子弹，
ifyou've guts, ifyour gun has bullets,
ifyou've票的航班，来解决吧。
ifyou've ticket for the flight, come there, let's settle it.
这是什么先生？ 你走极端你老了。
What's this sir? You're going overboard as you get old.
你为什么黑手党在这个年龄吗？
Why are you taking on mafia at this age?
黑手党的意思是黑社会，这意味着他们生活在地下，
Mafia mean underworld, it means they live underground,
我是不害怕的人生活在地下，
l'm not scared of people living underground,
我不尊重谁辜负以上，
l don't respect who live up above,
我不关心我旁边的人，
l don't care about people next to me,
押韵是完美的，它记下。
rhyming is perfect, make a note of it.
什么舅舅？
What's it uncle?
“复仇”，电影导演饶Nageshwara来自印度的，
'Revenge' Nageshwara Rao, a film director has come from lndia,
l必须显示他的位置，但，这里卡兰乔哈尔。
l must show him locations, but Karan Johar is here.
没问题，叔叔。 我管理我的弟子 - 谢谢亲爱的。
No problem, uncle. l'll manage with my disciples.- Thanks dear.
达苏，我们已经很晚了。 女士打电话给我们，我们已经走出去。
Dasu, we're getting late. Madam has called us, we've to go out.
L'来。
l'm coming.
不管你做，这是非常困难的捕获萨拉萨女士。
Whatever you may do, it is very difficult to trap Janaki madam.
是不可能实现的快感。
There's thrill in achieving the impossible.
我们必须做一些社会工作，我们为什么要操心电影？
We must do some social work, why should we bother about films?
这个工作也有自私的动机。
This job has selfish motive too.
自私吗？ 我不相信这一点。
Selfishness and you? l don't believe it.
不是我自己的自私，但自私的社会。
Not my own selfishness but selfishness for the society.
这听起来新的，什么是它的含义吗？
lt sounds new, what's the meaning of it?
我在Twitter上看到这个导演的鸣叫，
l've seen this director's tweets on Twitter,
他似乎在本质上非常激进，他不尊重女士，
he seems very radical in nature, he doesn't respect ladies,
他有没有对孩子的爱，他有不负责的社会，
he has no love for children, he has no responsibility ofthe society,
色情，暴力，杀戮，掠夺，伤害，令人作呕的想法！
sex, violence, killing, plundering, hurting, sickening thoughts!
lfwe改变了他的看法，并让他做电影球理念，
lfwe change his perception and get him to do a film on ball philosophy,
消息将轻易地传播到世界各地。
the message will spread around the world easily.
因为电影院是一个功能强大的媒体！
Because cinema is a powerful media!
不少有识之士的舞蹈看电影Saagara Sangamam后，
Many learnt dance after watching the film 'Saagara Sangamam',
学音乐后看电影'Shankarabharanam'。
learnt music after watching the film 'Shankarabharanam'.
拿起链看电影“湿婆”。
Picked up chains watching the film 'Shiva'.
闭嘴！ 总是不好比较。
Shut up! Always makes bad comparisons.
导演就在这里！
Director is here!
告诉戈皮协调员，我的舒适是非常重要的。
Tell coordinator Gopi that my comforts are very important.
戈皮给我们送来。 - 他在哪里？
Gopi sent us. - Where is he?
LS，他死了吗？
ls he dead?
他otherwork的，所以不能来。 于是，他给我们送来。
He has otherwork, so couldn't come. So he sent us.
他也有助理吗？ - 让我们冷静地坐下来谈！
He too has assistants? - Let's sit and talk coolly!
什么是说说孙达拉姆Babu的电影？ - 灾难先生。
What's the talk about Sundaram Babu's film?- Disaster sir.
它似乎所有的经销商都买农药。
lt seems all the distributors have bought pesticides too.
它似乎他们正在疯狂地滥用董事和英雄。
lt seems they're abusing wildly the director and the hero.
L'M'复仇'Nageshwara，饶自ltaly。
l'm 'Revenge' Nageshwara Rao from ltaly.
说说我的电影是什么？
What's the talk about my film?
什么人说你的电影？ 他们称它为块克星。
What would people say about your film? They call it as block buster.
LT买家和经销商似乎已经取代了神的照片与你。
lt seems buyers and distributors have replaced God's photos with yours.
LS呢？
ls it?
打击最大的行业，享受成功。
Biggest hit in industry, enjoy the success.
我来击败记录一个故事。
l'll come with a story to beat that record.
他是真正的导演。 不是有点ofjealousy。
He's real director. Not a bit ofjealousy.
我是做我的下一部电影的他，固定。
l'm doing my next film with him, fixed.
你为什么赞美一部电影，轰炸？
Why did you praise a film that has bombed?
lt'll是3个月，在他来之前，知道这是一个触发器。
lt'll be 3 months before he comes to know it's a flop.
那么我们的日期将被确认。
By then our dates would be confirmed.
时序是比人才更重要的在这个行业。
Timing is more important than talent in this industry.
它看起来不错，张贴在Twitter的。
lt looks good, post it on Twitter.
lfyou告诉你的故事，我会告诉你它的位置。
lfyou tell your story, l'll show you locations for it.
我的要求是故事。
My requirement is story.
一个故事的位置，而你在这里吗？
Are you here for locations without a story?
我打的东西，而位置狩猎时，对不对？
l'll hit upon something while on location hunting, right?
然后，你打的东西，甚至没有移动，先生。
Then, you've hit on something without even moving out, sir.
女士有一个现成的脚本。
Madam has a readymade script.
lfyou拍一部电影就可以了，它会创造新的纪录。
lfyou make a film on it, it'll create new records.
首先告诉我的故事。
First tell me the story.
一旦时间在Kottipalli时，住着一个亿万富翁。
Once upon a time in Kottipalli, there lived a billionaire.
LS他的名字Koteshwara饶？ - 号，饶VENKATESHWARA。
ls his name Koteshwara Rao? - No., Venkateshwara Rao.
随着数十亿十亿生活在他有一个强烈愿望。
Along with billions he had a strong wish to live among billions.
于是，他花了他所有的财富建立，
So he spent all his wealth to build,
医院，孤儿院，厕所，寺庙，学校，道路，池塘，
hospitals, orphanages, toilets, temples, schools, roads, ponds,
留下身无分文，转移到一个贫穷的小茅屋里支离破碎。
and was left penniless and shifted to a poor hut in tatters.
这不是一个故事，而是悲哀。
This is not a story but sorrow.
不仅L'VE一个伟大的冠军，太为这个故事。
Not only that l've a great title too for this story.
那是什么？
What's that?
“努力可以让男人为圣人'
'Effort can make men as saints'
成为圣徒，他们会做什么？
What would they do by becoming saints?
他们会乞求他们一样。
They'll beg like them.
LF我拍一部电影就可以了，他会不会乞讨，但我肯定乞求。
lf l make a film on it, he'll not beg, but l'll surely beg.
升了一个块克星故事的一个想法，而听到这个糟糕的故事。
l got an idea for a block buster story while hearing this lousy story.
记录它。
Record it.
这个故事有一个英雄和5个女主人公。
This story has one hero and 5 heroines.
在第一现场，
ln the first scene,
第一女主角蒙娜丽莎敲打她的头在墙上的英雄被杀害。
first heroine Mona is killed by hero by banging her head on wall.
如果我们倾斜了相机，从美丽的尸体，
ifwe tilt up the camera from the beautiful dead body,
一个致命的歌曲！ - 什么是这里的歌，先生？
a deadly song! - What's the song here, sir?
Thaman会照顾它，记录它，你的男人。
Thaman will take care of it, you record it, man.
切它，它是第二女主角拉尼，
Cut it, it's second heroine Rani,
英雄拿起一个大的巨石和摔破拉尼要杀死她的头，
hero picks up a big boulder and smashes the head of Rani to kill her,
把它剪断，喜剧场景如下！ - 喜剧场景在这里？
cut it, comedy scene follows! - Comedy scene here?
两具尸体被对方的讽刺作品。 记录吧！
Two corpses were making satires on each other. Record it!
现在第三的女主角Mamatha，
Now the third heroine Mamatha,
他拉她到浴缸，
he pulls her to the bathtub,
推她进去，并在她脖子上的邮票，
pushes her into it and stamps on her neck,
杀害她的卑鄙。
kills her dastardly.
切，战斗场景。 - 谁能与他交战呢？
Cut it, fight scene. - Who would he fight with?
随着女孩的男朋友。
With the girl's boy friends.
LS女孩人品不好？ - 非常坏。
ls the girl such a bad character? - Very bad.
如果没有，为什么会英雄杀死的女孩呢？
lf not why would the hero kill the girls then?
当时发生了什么事，先生？
What happened then, sir?
得到的故事，直到那时，2钉晚上将完成它。
Got the story till then only, 2 pegs at night will finish it.
我想这个故事的APT位置。
l want apt locations for this story.
LS这个位置的故事给你好吗？
ls this location okay to you for the story?
任何位置实在是太多了，他的故事。
Any location is too much for his story.
记录它。
Record it.
修复帧十暴徒你像疯狗。
Fix the frame and ten goons are coming at you like mad dogs.
为什么我在现实中看到的视觉效果呢？
Why am l seeing the visuals in real?
仍处于宿醉，他们是真正的暴徒。
Still in hangover, they're real goons.
球击中墙壁上总是会反弹回来。
The ball hit on wall will always bounce back.
我抓住一个团伙被警方抓到作弊游客。
l got a gang caught by police for cheating tourists.
他们会一直送他们到我采取报复。
They would've sent them to take revenge on me.
不，他们来到我身边。
No, they're here for me.
他们疯狂，这意味着他们是“疯狂”罗伯特的男子。
They're coming crazily, it means they're 'crazy' Robert's men.
没有，他们未来的我。 - 不，对我来说。
No, they're coming for me. - No, for me.
l表示对我，对不对？ - 太升说，对我来说，对不对？
l said for me, right? - l too said for me, right?
停止你的论点。
Stop your argument.
lfwe被抓住，他们会诽谤我们。
lfwe get caught, they'll lynch us.
住手！ 我们为什么要运行时，他们已经做了错误的事情吗？
Stop! Why should we run when they've done the wrong thing?
我们陷入死ifwe're。
We're dead ifwe're caught.
你死亡了，你能不能考虑他们吗？
You took on death, can't you take on them?
第.. - 什么？
No... - What no?
你想从山上跳到你的死亡。
You wanted to jump to your death from a mountain.
你为什么不跳，而不是他们？
Why don't you jump on them instead?
如何能采取他们吗？
How can l take on them?
想想他们作为秋刀鱼巴努的男朋友不是暴徒。
Think them as Saira Banu's boyfriends not goons.
还记得她是怎么骗你。
Remember how she cheated you.
所有的精力转移到拳头。
Transfer all your energy to fist.
每个新书冲必须像一个球送他们到边界。 去！
Each ofyour punch must send them like a ball into the boundary. Go!
罗伯特在意大利太有网络。
Robert has network in ltaly too.
你觉得呢？ 黑手党可不是闹着玩的。
What do you think then? Mafia is no joke.
这是一个好球！
That's a good shot!
你看，他如何击败他们！
Look, how he's beating them!
看看他是如何击败他们，夫人！
Look how he's beating them, madam!
什么权力，你的夫人！
What a power you've madam!
你打他们，并说这是她的力量。
You beat them and say it's her power.
L切勿举手秋刀鱼是谁骗了我。
l never raised hand on Saira who cheated me.
如何能处理这么多的人？
How can l handle so many men?
它的太太灵感。
lt's madam's inspiration.
女士的话激励着我。 女士的力量把我激怒了。
Madam's words motivated me. Madam's power provoked me.
伟大的创新是赞誉。
Great innovation is praise.
我的直觉，你可以把国家原子弹弹入。
l've gut feeling you can turn country bomb into atom bomb.
你可以把煤变成金子。
You can turn coal into gold.
您可以创建一个游泳池的海啸。
You can create Tsunami in a swimming pool.
一个喷嚏，你可以产生一个气旋。
You can produce a cyclone with a sneeze.
你可以让一个跛脚的功夫冠军。
You can make Kung-Fu champion of a lame.
你可以做一个哑巴做模仿。
You can make a dumb to do mimicry.
我的直觉，你可以把国家原子弹弹入。
l've gut feeling you can turn country bomb into atom bomb.
你可以把煤变成金子。
You can turn coal into gold.
你不吃，而不做一件好事，姐姐。
You don't eat without doing a good deed, sister.
你为什么要疯狂地吃吗？
Why are you eating madly?
我已经为自己赢得吃了生活的权利，而不做一件好事。
l've earned myself a right to eat for life without doing a good deed.
生活时间成就是什么？
What's that life time achievement?
不止是一个或两个，
Notjust one or two,
我做了一个商人奄奄一息的彼得，
l've made a businessman of dying Peter,
我挑口袋詹姆斯遍布米兰著名，
l've made pick-pocket James famous all over Milan,
我做了一个乞丐像达苏著名作家。
l've made a beggar like Dasu a famous writer.
一个男孩像拉玛饶击败了大绿巨人像暴徒。
A boy like Rama Rao beat up big hulk like goons.
我的感觉，如果我在我的这么大的权力，为什么要限制自己升？
l feel if l've so much power in me, why should l limit myself?
这就是为什么我来决定。 - 那是什么？
That's why l've come to a decision. - What's that?
升要创建一个像安娜・哈扎尔的运动。
l want to create a movement like Anna Hazare.
l必须停止拉闸限电。 降低汽油价格。
l must stop the power cuts. Reduce petrol price.
把禁止。 你会禁止？
Bring prohibition. What will you prohibit?
如果别人去瞎具有功率大，你瞎你的清白。
lf people go blind with power, you're blind with your innocence.
首先，确保禁止上楼。 - 你在说什么？
First ensure prohibition upstairs. - What are you talking??
达苏和拉玛饶欺骗你。 他们饮用楼上。
Dasu and Rama Rao are fooling you. They're drinking upstairs.
绝不会做我的门徒。 来吧，让我们检查一下。
My disciples will never do that. Come, let's check.
我们还活着，因为我们的祖先的善行和你的功夫。
We're still alive because of our ancestors' good deeds and your Kung Fu.
如果没有，我们就已经牺牲这个疯太太的清白。
lf not we would've been sacrificed to this mad madam's innocence.
他们来找我，不是她。
They came for me not for her.
他们从秋刀鱼巴努？ - 她是谁？
Are they from Saira Banu? - Who is she?
你重复她的名字，像一个孩子寻求巧克力。
You repeat her name like a kid asking for chocolate.
女孩子都喜欢去安慰一个哭泣的男人。
Girls like to console a crying man.
这就是为什么我创建的，无特色的字符。
That's why l created that characterless character.
随着一名舞蹈演员，战斗机，有一个作家，你太。
Along with a dancer and fighter, there's a writer too in you.
达苏，你说喝酒可以让我忘记秋刀鱼巴努。
Dasu, you said drinking can make me forget Saira Banu.
为什么我还记得她吗？
Why am l still remembering her?
这是目的饮品。 目的 - 为什么失败呢？
That's the purpose of drinks. - Why did the purpose fail then?
我觉得你受伤太深。
l think you're hurt too deeply.
不止是我，整个国家的男孩的痛苦，因为秋刀鱼等作弊。
Notjust me, entire country's boys are suffering because of cheats like Saira.
LF我没有见过她的'Bommarillu'和分离50天的“爱失败”
lf l hadn't met her in 'Bommarillu' and separated on 50 days of 'Love Failure'
我的整个生命，会一直“快乐的日子”！
my entire life would've been 'Happy Days'!
然后，Siddarth手也有你的爱情故事。
Then, Siddarth hand is also there in your love story.
不止是我的爱情故事，
Notjust in my love story,
Siddarth的手是有非常深，每个人的爱情故事。
Siddarth's hand is there very deep in everyone's love story.
他让女孩参观咖啡天内。
He made girls to visit Coffee days.
他呵护女孩的朋友，在他的电影，
He pampers girl friends in his films,
看着女孩问我像，
watching that girls ask me to behave like that,
咖啡天会配合我的大众脸吗？ 你说得对。
would Coffee days match with my mass face? You're right.
而这个“DIL”拉朱，
And this 'Dil' Raju,
在一侧，他使青年的爱情故事，说没有爱情的生活是浪费，
on one side he makes youth love stories saying life without love is waste,
另一边，他做电影，说家中长辈是正确的，
another side he makes films saying family elders are right,
并会把我们弄糊涂，
and confuses us,
我们已经死于与他们最近的社交网络，
already we're dying with them and recently social networks,
你有没有看到这个词本身，有一个净？
did you see, there's a net in the word itself?
它意味着用网捕获男孩。
lt means trapping boys with a net.
女孩从来没有读过书，但总是在facebook上。
Girls never read books but are always on facebook.
他们是真正的至少有吗？
Are they genuine at least there?
没有！ 名称是迦腻色迦但照片是ANUSHKA的，
No! Name is Kanishka but photo is Anushka,
名字是Sangeetha，照片是萨曼莎，
name is Sangeetha, photo is Samantha,
实际上摧毁这个国家是不是真实的东西，
actually the real thing that's destroying this country isn't,
选举，腐败，2G或3G，但单?！
elections, corruption, 2G or 3G, but single G!
G的女孩！
G for girls!
酒吧，夜总会，餐馆，度假村，商场，复用，
Pubs, clubs, restaurants, resorts, malls, multiplexes,
forwhom所有这些都建立吗？
forwhom all these are built?
出生后，他们的父亲，长大后，自己的男朋友，
After birth their fathers, after growing up, their boyfriends,
结婚后，她们的丈夫，破坏和毁掉他们马不停蹄。
after marriage, their husbands, to destroy and ruin them non-stop.
告诉他们禁止所有这些一天！
Tell them to ban all these for one day!
LF 印度不会在30分钟内，超过美国
lf lndia doesn't overtake America in 30 minutes,
我剃我的胡子，我的鼻子擦地面上！
l'll shave my moustache, rub my nose on ground!
你为什么这么激动？ 你的意思是所有的女人都这样的吗？
Why are you getting so excited? You mean all women are like that?
除一人外！ - 是谁呢？
Except one! - Who is it?
lsn't我们的夫人夫人？ 男孩吗？
lsn't our madam a lady? Boy?
LS她淑女男孩？
ls she lady boy?
呸！ 她是一个天使！
Yuck! She's an angel!
你有没有观察萨拉萨夫人？
Did you ever observe Janaki madam?
我看到她的善良，从来没有见过她的正确。
l've seen her goodness only never saw her properly.
她像女神玛哈拉卡斯的现代礼服。
She's like Goddess Mahalakshmi in modern dress.
穿lfshe纱丽，她女神Kanakamahalakshmi！
lfshe wears a sari, she's Goddess Kanakamahalakshmi!
我们怎样才能喝她的弟子？
How can we drink as her disciples?
如果夫人来知道这一点呢？
What if madam comes to know this?
她敏感的心怎么会被削弱了！
How her sensitive heart would weaken!
是的，如果夫人的天使，lnky和Pinky侧天使。
Yes, if madam is angel, lnky and Pinky are side angels.
他们都可能死震惊！
they both may die in shock!
第一次在我的生活升喝了你听。
First time in my life l drank listening to you.
我已经决定这是最后一次！
l've decided this is the last!
看看他们！
Look at them!
放松，他们走了。
Relax, they're gone.
为什么你不赞美太太直接，为什么你嘲笑所有的女孩第一次吗？
Why didn't you praise madam directly, why did you deride all girls first?
LF升嘲笑所有其他只有赞美她，她会觉得之一类。
lf l deride all others and praise her only, she'll feel one ofthe kind.
冲击次数将伟大的，懂吗？
lmpact will b great, got it?
拿起瓶子，让我们喝一杯。
Pick the bottle, let's have a drink.
无瓶，你把它弄坏了，对不对？
No bottle, you broke it, right?
疯狂的达苏，L打破了一瓶水，并有满瓶是唯一的。
Mad Dasu, l broke water bottle and full bottle is there only.
你吓唬我，饶！
You're frightening me, Rao!
荣获“球仍然在为我们拍摄了昨晚反弹？
Won' the ball be still bouncing for the shot we gave last night?
不管它可能是它会不会爱上你的篮子 - 为什么不呢？
Whatever it may be it'll not fall in your basket.- Why not?
萨拉萨夫人希望成为德雷莎修女，
Janaki madam would wish to become Mother Teresa,
她永远也不会希望成为饶Mrs.Rama。
she'll never wish to become Mrs.Rama Rao.
我我喜欢Kanakamahalakshmi？
Am l like Kanakamahalakshmi?
夫人猜怎么能在我的心里是什么？ - 我没有得到它。
How could madam guess what's in my heart?- l don't get it.
我改造你，不能。升getjudge此？
l've reformed you, can't l getjudge this?
我知道你讨厌赞美，夫人，但请不要阻止我今天。
l know you hate praise, madam, but please don't stop me today.
你为什么要挣扎呢？ 来吧，拉玛饶！
Why are you struggling? Come out, Rama Rao!
没什么，升想，这是所有的小细节。
Nothing, l wanted to be little detail, that's all.
任何人会发疯，头发！
Any man would go crazy for that hair!
颈部颈部..
Neck...neck..
颈部项链道路。
Neck is necklace road.
肚脐！
Navel!
不要发言猥亵。 腰围是国家高速公路。
Don't speak indecently. Waist is national highway.
可能已经工作了R＆B，他们再也看不到任何东西。
May have worked for R & B, they can't see anything else.
诗人拥有的东西在这个世界上，有权进行比较。
A poet has the right to compare with anything in this world.
在你有一个很好的诗人。
There's a good poet in you.
真的是很幸运的女孩，谁娶你。
The girl who marries you is really very lucky.
在刚才参观了寺庙，发行。
Visited a temple just now, take offering.
一切都会好起来。
Everything will be fine.
饶，你不是一个普通的击球手，
Rao, you're not an ordinary batsman,
你任何射门，球会六去！
any shot from you, the ball will go for a six!
如果没有你......
Without you...
如果没有你......亲爱的
Without you...darling
等待你整日整夜...
Waiting for you all day and night...
你是我的心和灵魂......
You're my heart and soul...
你是我的月光...... 你是我的光......
You're my moonbeam... you're my light...
你是我的目的地......
You're my destination...
倒升平板为你... 坐进可爱的动作...
l fell flat for you... Got into lovely action...
升跟着你......
l followed you...
倒升禁售爱...
l fell into the lock-up of love...
下跌到一个未知的反...
Fell into an unknown trans...
真是一个神奇的女孩...
What a magical girl...
我的生活是一个危险的像一个天使诞生...
A danger to my life is born like an angel...
L'要死......我住在呼吸机的新书美容...
l'm dying...l'm living on the ventilator ofyour beauty...
景点的吸引力...
Attraction...attraction...
审议....审议...
Deliberation....deliberation...
L请与您的视线？ L'得到你陶醉......
May l wipe it with your sight? l'm getting enchanted by you...
在这个世界上的人后，你是...
Anyone in this world is after you...
请问你谈谈吗？ 愿升抚弄你吗？
May l talk to you? May l fondle you?
你ajasmine的树枝...
You're ajasmine twig...
你的蓝眼睛，迷人...
Your blue eyes are mesmerising...
你的微笑是一个华丽的导弹... 就拿我的生命，我的爱...
Your smile is a flowery missile... Take my life, my love...
DLG巴拉拉姆部门自豪，真诚的人员，
DlG Balaram, a sincere officer who made the department proud,
它真的很不幸他下降到黑手党的子弹，
it's really unfortunate he fell to the bullets of mafia,
谁曾在他的团队的年轻officerAdhi ...
young officerAdhi who worked in his team...
他是一个灵感，许多像我这样的年轻军官。
He's an inspiration to many young officers like me.
我生命的目标是赶上的Baadshah谁杀了这样一个伟大的人员。
My life's aim is to catch Baadshah who killed such a great officer.
我准备牺牲自己的生命，去实现它。
l'm ready to sacrifice my life to achieve it.
如果沉默了学校的主人，ifflexible一个舞蹈大师，
lf silent a school master, ifflexible a dance master,
iffit钻高手，他们把他们误以为我！
iffit a drill master, they took on mistaking me for them!
现在已经开始追捕！
The hunt has begun now!
新森林官员也不能阻止我！
The new forest officer too can't stop me!
什么？ - 显示他剪辑。
What? - Show him the clip.
如果沉默了学校的主人，ifflexible一个舞蹈大师，
lf silent a school master, ifflexible a dance master,
iffit钻高手，他们把他们误以为我！
iffit a drill master, they took on mistaking me for them!
现在已经开始追捕！
The hunt has begun now!
新森林官员也不能阻止我！
The new forest officer too can't stop me!
什么是你的制片人说吗？
What is your producer saying?
他说，你的决策是长于实拍。
He said your making is longer than actual film.
傻男人！ 告诉他把它发送到电视频道，无需切割框架。
Silly man! Tell him to send it to TV channels without cutting a frame.
你觉得如何呢？ - 它的超乎寻常的！
How do you feel about it? - lt's extra-ordinary!
lsn't，拉玛饶？
lsn't it, Rama Rao?
如果艺人10％ofwhat，董事职务，每部电影将是一个silverjubilee命中。
lf artistes do 10% ofwhat director did, every film would be a silverjubilee hit.
lsn't达苏？ - 是的老板。
lsn't it, Dasu? - Yes boss.
董事已表明了我们10的化身！
Director has shown us 10 incarnations!
你想和我说话吗？
You wanted to talk to me?
你要回到明天lnd??ia，对不对？
You're going back to lndia tomorrow, right?
你想给我公司？
Would you like to give me company?
没有，拉玛饶是一个很好的舞者。
No, Rama Rao is a good dancer.
，lfyou正确使用他，他会成为另一个NTR！
lfyou use him properly, he would become another NTR!
我知道自己的潜力，拉玛饶！
l know your potential, Rama Rao!
请你阻止它？
Will you please stop it?
你称赞他和他的感觉害羞，
You're praising him and he's feeling shy,
进入影院领域为容易进入影院呢？
is entering cinema field as easy as entering a theatre?
有许多伟大的人在这里工作！
How many great people worked here!
有了这样的大导演，在这里，
With such great directors here,
每一个白痴想进入该领域的驳船！
every idiot wants to barge into the field!
什么苏里亚？ 该死的白痴！
What Surya? Bloody idiot!
谁是白痴？ 你是个白痴。
Who is idiot? You're an idiot.
你的电影是愚蠢的！
Your films are foolish!
你比较自己到KV雷迪？
Are you comparing yourself to K V Reddy?
告诉我，一部电影由KV雷迪？
Tell me one film made by K V Reddy?
'Mosagaallaku Mosagaadu
'Mosagaallaku Mosagaadu'
它由行动王KSR达斯！
lt was made by action king K S R Dass!
你冷静下来，我会和他谈谈，夫人！ 不要感情用事。
You calm down, l'll talk to him, madam! Don't get emotional.
升离开她，因为她是个女孩。
l left her because she's a girl.
我砍你一分为二！ 你没看到我的视频？
l'll cut you into two! Didn't you see my making video?
猛砸他！
Bash him!
她问KV雷迪的电影和你告诉KSR达斯的电影。
She asked K V Reddy's film and you told K S R Dass's film.
'Mosagaallaku Mosagaadu
'Mosagaallaku Mosagaadu'
刚才她说。
Just now she said that.
那么，告诉我另一部电影。
So, tell me another film.
另一部电影...'Pandanti Kapuram'。
Another film...'Pandanti Kapuram'.
'Pandanti Kapuram'？
'Pandanti Kapuram'?
它的导演是拉克希米迪帕克。
lt was directed by Lakshmi Deepak.
你这么好的一个关于电影的知识吗？
Do you've such a good knowledge about films?
我知道得多。 - 更多吗？
l know much more. - More?
谁是第一个收件人的的达达萨希卜Phalke奖泰卢固语电影？
Who is the first recipient of Dada Saheb Phalke award for Telugu films?
如果L告诉正确答案，你会打败？
Will you beat if l tell correct answer?
升打败你告诉错误的答案。
l beat you for telling wrong answer.
Nageshwara饶了它在1990年，
Nageshwara Rao got it in 1990,
Bommireddy纳拉辛哈・雷迪于1974年，得到了它 - 他是谁？
Bommireddy Narasimha Reddy got it in 1974,- Who is he?
BN雷迪！
B N Reddy!
我知道关于BN雷迪的建设者，我不知道有电影导演。
l know about B N Reddy a builder, l didn't know there was film director.
你知不知道关于BN雷迪？
Don't you know about B N Reddy?
不要让紧张和破坏你的健康，请出来。
Don't get tensed and spoil your health, please come out.
你毁了她的心情。
You ruined her mood.
他们击败我喜欢我的学校老师Kripanandham主。
They beat me like my school teacher Kripanandham master.
应记录呢？
Shall l record this too?
你总是这么酷，你怎么能这么激动吗？
You're so cool always, how could you get so emotional?
他怎么敢虐待你！
How dare he abused you!
他基本上是一个坏男人。 不止是我，他会滥用任何人。
He's basically a bad man. Notjust me, he'll abuse anyone.
如果他滥用和你的朋友，它的不同 - 为什么？
lt's different if he abuses you and others.- Why?
l表示不同的，对不对？ - 我会问为什么？
l said different, right? - l'm asking why?
拉玛饶，你刺激性我！
Rama Rao, you're irritating me!
我说你是来自别人，这是所有不同。
l said you're different from others, that's all.
L'非常接近实现我的目标。
l'm very near in achieving my goal.
无人能阻止Baadshah的，直到他达到他的目的！
Nobody can stop Baadshah till he achieves his aim!
Baadshah谁在黑道上引起了巨大轰动，
Baadshah who created a sensation in the underworld,
知道他为什么现在的沉默，
to know why he's silent now,
你必须知道关于皇家赌场在澳门，
you must know about Royal Casino in Macau,
Baadshah的父亲Dhanraj用于运行皇家赌场，
Baadshah's father Dhanraj used to run Royal Casino,
苦行僧BHAI的收入的50％来自皇家赌场，
Sadhu Bhai's 50% of income used to come from Royal Casino,
苦行僧BHAI谁征服了整个东南亚，
Sadhu Bhai who conquered entire South East Asia,
他也不敢进入香港。
he couldn't dare enter Hong Kong.
原因是暴力的维克多和他的儿子狠约翰尼。
reason for it is Violent Victor and his son Ruthless Johnny.
随着香港作为基地，Victorwho跑贩毒集团和贩卖人口印度的，
With Hong Kong as base, Victorwho ran drug mafia and human trafficking in lndia,
他奠定了他的眼睛上首次Dhanraj的赌场，
he laid his eyes first time on Dhanraj's casino,
香港胜者面积。 安全的钱存入??银行。
Hong Kong is Victor's area. Deposit the money safely in bank.
被困Dhanraj的杂种。
Got trapped, you Dhanraj's mongrels.
什么的码数OFTHE更衣室？
What's the code number ofthe locker?
告诉我，如果不是我砍你。
Tell me, if not l'll cut you.
那是谁的生日？
Whose birthday is that?
你有信息日期，厢式车路线，更衣室代码也。
You got information about date, van route, and locker code also.
但不知道Dh??anraj的儿子狮子谁最近进入这一领域。
But didn't know about Dhanraj's son lion who has entered the field recently.
这是你最大的错误。
That's your biggest mistake.
这狮子的名称是Baadshah！
That lion's name is Baadshah!
lfyou不敢惹Baadshah，声音会是固体！
lfyou dare touch Baadshah, the sound will be solid!
这是香港，这是我的父亲维克多的地区。
This is Hong Kong, this is my dad Victor's area.
球场虽然是你的，本场比赛是我的。
Though the pitch is yours, the match is mine.
告诉你爸，Baadshah已经来临！
Tell your dad that Baadshah has arrived!
如果Baadshah决定，战争将成为一个片面的。
lf Baadshah decides, war will become one sided.
维克多拿到了棍子！
Victor got the stick!
强尼几乎浸湿了他的裤子。
Jonny almost wetted his pants.
Baadshah，我的儿子！
Baadshah, my son!
现在，我了解我的儿子长大了，他们已经了解他是一个男人！
Now l've understood my son is grown up and they've understood he's a man!
你第一次在香港维克多咬尘埃。
First time you've made Victor bite dust in Hong Kong.
你为什么紧张？
Why are you tensed?
明天是嫂嫂的生日，
Tomorrow is sister-in-law's birthday,
像每年一样，我已经安排了特别祈祷她的名字在寺庙，
like every year, l've arranged for special prayers on her name in temple,
但寺庙是维克多的地区。
but the temple is in Victor's area.
这不现在有权进入该地区。
lt's not right to enter the area now.
叔叔，永不退缩offfrom的承诺，固定日期，这不是男子气概。
Uncle, never back offfrom promise given, fixed date, it's not manliness.
无Baadshah ...
No Baadshah...
谁怕是奴隶，吓唬谁是Baadshah！
One who fears is slave, one who frightens is Baadshah!
巴伊，该名男子谁击败约翰尼已经进入我们的地区。
Bhai, the man who beat Johnny has entered our area.
走的快！
Go fast!
升想隆重庆祝你母亲的生日，她还活着的时候。
l wanted to celebrate your mother's birthday grandly when she was alive.
但我不能。 现在l可以，但她是不是还活着。
But l couldn't. Now l can but she's not alive.
走...走...走的快！
Go...go...go fast!
在哪里Baadshah？ - 他离开，BHAI。
Where's Baadshah? - He left, Bhai.
你为什么让他走？
Why did you let him go?
看见他，BHAI吓坏了。
Got scared on seeing him, Bhai.
告诉我，维克拉姆。
Tell me, Vikram.
好吧。
Okay.
2年后，，苦行僧BHAI已被称为突发的会议。
Sadhu Bhai has called a sudden meeting after 2 years.
他要我跟你一起去。 - 会议在哪里？
He wants me to come with you. - Where's the meeting?
苦行僧BHAI不会透露在现场，直到最后一分钟。
Sadhu Bhai won't reveal the spot till last minute.
苦行僧BHAI，我的儿子Baadshah！ - Ofwhich国家？
Sadhu bhai, my son Baadshah! - Ofwhich country?
他出生时，我的父亲赢得了冠军'Baadshah摔跤。
He was born when my father won the title 'Baadshah' in wrestling.
从那时起，我们叫他，而不是他的真实姓名Baadshah。
Ever since then we call him as Baadshah instead of his real name.
Dhanraj，你已经工作了20年，我
Dhanraj, you've been working for 20 years with me,
它意味着升信任你！
it means l trust you!
lfthat是真的，我们将不会被搜身。
lfthat was true, we won't get frisked.
恐惧！
Fear!
升很喜欢你的胆量，当你打约翰尼维克多面积内。
l liked your guts when you hit Johnny inside Victor's area.
我喜欢你的态度。
Now l like your attitude.
这就是为什么我是给你一个机会。
That's why l'm giving you an opportunity.
这不是一个机会，如果你给你俩的必要性。
lt's not an opportunity ifyou give it foryour necessity.
什么工作？
What's the job?
安东尼，来自肯尼亚一个男人谁提供一个容器，
Antony, a man who came from Kenya to deliver a container,
维克多的男子绑架了他，你必须收回他，
Victor's men kidnapped him, you must recover him,
因为容器ofvery高价值 - 多少钱？
because the container is ofvery high value.- How much?
我给澳门。
Give Macau to me.
你怎么敢把条件给我的老板！
How dare you put conditions to my boss!
离开他！
Leave him!
澳门lfyou recoverAntony，都是你的。
lfyou recoverAntony, Macau is all yours.
这些孩子是水灾灾民。 水灾灾民。
These children are flood victims. Flood victims.
有没有人询问他们。
There's no one to inquire about them.
他们不知道我们正在做的业务与自己的器官。
They don't know we're doing business with their organs.
安全转移到实验室。
Shift them safely to lab.
交出孩子到印度n大使馆。
Hand over the children to lndian Embassy.
梁锦松，约翰尼在哪里？ - 安东尼？
Where's Antony, Johnny? - Antony?
我不知道什么。 - 我知道你不知道。
l don't know anything. - l know you don't know.
因为安东尼被绑架我的人。
Because Antony was kidnapped by my men.
你为什么要杀死他，Baadshah？
Why did you kill him, Baadshah?
升答应交出安东尼下午4时。
l promised to hand over Antony by 4 pm.
Baadshah将永不退缩跟踪自己的诺言，承诺。
Baadshah will never back track his promise, commitment.
本场比赛，我们打你父亲不知情的情况下与苦行僧，
The game which we're playing without your father's knowledge with Sadhu,
我们已经到了最后阶段。
we've reached the final stage.
从这里开始，我们必须非常小心。
We've to be very careful from here.
直到我们实现我们的目标，想想唯一目的，叔叔。
Till we achieve our aim, think about only purpose, uncle.
没有潜伏的危险。
Not about lurking dangers.
你交给安东尼，你答应。
You've handed over Antony as you promised.
就拿它。
Take it.
Baadshah绝不会拿任何东西，他会征服它。
Baadshah will never take anything, he'll conquer it.
想起他，你就完蛋了......
Think of him, you're finished...
弓你的头，向他致敬......
Bow your head and salute him...
他是亚历山大在赛场上...... 他Baadshah！
He's Alexander in the arena... He's Baadshah!
像刀片一样锋利的武士刀可以切割任何敌人的神经... 他是亚历山大在赛场上...... 他Baadshah！
Sharp like the blade of Samurai sword which can cut nerves of any enemy... He's Alexander in the arena... He's Baadshah!
像刀片一样锋利的武士刀可以切割任何敌人的神经...
Sharp like the blade of Samurai sword which can cut nerves of any enemy...
他走的是迅速...冒险... 运行刺他的敌人不寒而栗......
His walk is swift...adventurous... Runs shivers down the spines of his enemies...
他不会休息，直到他到达顶部统治...
He won't rest till he reaches the top to rule over all...
将不会停止，直到胜利完成...
Won't stop till the victory is complete...
世界属于在yourfeet如果你把握机会...
The world falls at yourfeet ifyou take chances...
无与伦比的能量和无限的热情，是他的拿手好戏。
Unparalleled energy and unlimited enthusiasm is his forte...
我们信息苦行僧BHAI是发送容器负荷RDX香港。
We've information that Sadhu bhai is sending a container load of RDX from Hong Kong.
我已经谈过，那里的专员。
l've already talked to the Commissioner there.
与您的团队，并在香港本身停止代销。
Go with your team and stop the consignment in Hong Kong itself.
为什么我们应该去那里呢？ 我们不能在这里提醒所有的端口？
Why should we go there sir? Can't we alert all the ports here?
他们会使用的海岸线，这些货物并不端口。
They'll use the coastline for such consignments not ports.
印度有超过6000公里的海岸线。
lndia has a coastline of over 6000 kms.
他们可以在任何地方卸载它！
They can unload it anywhere!
到现在的每一点的RDX一样，只有达到印度。
Till now every bit of RDX reached lndia like that only.
我会立刻离开我的球队，先生。
l'll leave immediately with my team, sir.
保守秘密，直到操作完成。
Keep it confidential till the operation is completed.
不要放弃任何细节给你的团队也。
Don't give any details to your team also.
苦行僧BHAI，你试图征服香港多年，但失败了，
Sadhu bhai, you tried many years to conquer Hong Kong but failed,
现在我是放弃香港，
now l'm surrendering Hong Kong to you,
我是不感兴趣的东西，
l'm not interested in anything,
只有一个利益L'已经在我的生活中是Baadshah的死亡！
the only one interest l've in my life is Baadshah's death!
我需要你的帮助来实现它。
l need your help to achieve it.
他是我的男人。
He's my man.
如果他是，他不会采取澳门从你。
lf he was, he wouldn't have taken Macau from you.
Baadshah起到了戏剧澳门绑架安东尼。
Baadshah played a drama to take Macau by kidnapping Antony.
你还记得吧？ 今天是大卫的儿子的婚事。
You remember, right? Today is David's son's marriage.
出席婚姻与叔叔。
You attend the marriage with uncle.
大卫叔叔非常接近我们。
David uncle is very close to us.
每个人都结婚了，当他打算结婚？
Everyone is getting married, when is he going to marry?
为什么要嫁给他吗？ - LS，他一个小孩子吗？
Why marry him off now? - ls he a little kid?
嫂嫂一直活着，他已经结婚了长回来。
Had sister-in-law been alive, he would've got married long back.
叔叔，忘了我的婚姻，让我们参加，婚姻。
Uncle, forget about my marriage, let's attend that marriage.
巴伊Baadshah已经离开圣保罗教堂参加大卫的儿子的婚事。
Bhai, Baadshah has left to St.Paul's church to attend David's son's marriage.
澳门市长来我们的赌场，我觉得你的存在会更好。
Macau Mayor is coming to our casino, l think your presence would be better.
我参加你叔叔结婚。
l'll attend the marriage with your uncle.
我弟弟他的生命献给我。
My brother dedicated his life for me.
对我来说，他活到最后一刻。 他为我而死。
He lived till the last moment for me. He died for me.
我们决不能饶恕维克多。
We mustn't spare Victor.
维克多并不孤单，苦行僧BHAI是这背后的攻击。
Victor is not alone, Sadhu bhai is also behind this attack.
为什么会苦行僧BHAI尝试杀我呢？
Why would Sadhu bhai try to kill me?
他想杀我不要你。
He wanted to kill me not you.
l必须听到Baadshah去世的消息！
l must hear the news of Baadshah's death!
升工作20年忠实苦行僧
l worked 20 years loyally for Sadhu,
升走散了，我的妻子，
l got separated from my wife,
他怎么敢密??谋杀死我的儿子！
how dare he conspires to kill my son!
升工作这些年来，这样的男人吗？
Did l work all these years for such a man?
我们必须订购，我们绝不能听命于苦行僧。
We must order, we mustn't take orders from Sadhu.
我们的勇气，必须制止他。
Our courage must put an end to him.
维克多，苦行僧BHAI，你大爷的死亡背后的每个人都必须死。
Victor, Sadhu bhai, everyone behind your uncle's death must die.
必须是只有黑手党Baadshah。
There must be only one Baadshah for mafia.
一定是你！
And it must be you!
他杀死了我的儿子，他抢走澳门从苦行僧BHAI，
He killed my son, he took away Macau from Sadhu Bhai,
他不会停止，
he won't stop with that,
新加坡，马来西亚，香港，菲律宾。
Singapore, Malaysia, Hong Kong, Philippines.
他的野心是统治整个南亚！
his ambition is to rule over entire South Asia!
不需要那么多的男人，BHAI。
No need of so many men, bhai.
L'就杀Baadshah的，他的父亲和所有其他人，
l'll kill Baadshah, his father and all others,
我会杜绝这个问题。
l'll put an end to the problem.
没有用的，只是意图杀死敌人，
No use of having just intent to kill enemy,
你必须有内容。
you must have content.
今天，你会死在这里。
Today you'll die here.
我的祖父没有名字，我使用它作为我的墓志铭。
My grandfather didn't name me to use it as my epitaph.
要被写入历史！
To be written in history!
lfyou想住是Baadshah下，
lfyou want to live be under Baadshah,
如果你们想死，站在前Baadshah！
ifyou want to die, stand before Baadshah!
维克多的比赛结束了！ 清场！
Victor's game is over! The field is clear!
你是唯一一个离开。
You're the only one left.
LT碰我，也不是那么容易。
lt isn't so easy to touch me.
韩国人，马来西亚人，lndonesians，我杀了大家谁反对我，
Koreans, Malaysians, lndonesians, l've killed everyone who opposed me,
并创建这个帝国！
and created this empire!
Baadshah这里征服帝国。
Baadshah is here to conquer that empire.
从今天开始Baadshah的规则！
From today Baadshah's rule begins!
时间内没有苦行僧BHAI的的黑手党章也就结束了。
Within no time Sadhu bhai's chapter in mafia will be over.
你不具备这种能力。
You don't have that capacity.
边界炸毁为Baa??dshah的耐力！
Boundaries blow up for Baadshah's stamina!
刚苦行僧BHAI战争是没有一样容易完成维克多的团伙。
Gang war with Sadhu bhai isn't as easy as finishing Victor's gang.
LF Baadshah决定战争将成为一个片面的。
lf Baadshah decides war will become one sided.
升开始你的战争。
l began the war for you.
我会结束它与你同在。
l'll end it with you.
维克多的住所??Kowlan：香港
Victor's residence Kowlan, Hong Kong
你都感觉有点不安。
You all are feeling little restless.
弟兄，升瞒着你，犯了许多小错误，因为童年
Bro, l committed many small mistakes since childhood without telling you,
升希望有一天来清洁它，
l wanted to come clean about it someday,
但你死了，你应该怎么办呢？
but you died, what should l do now?
你可以告诉我。
You can confess to me.
当升是在第十L舱，感觉像亲吻哥哥的女朋友凯瑟琳。
When l was in tenth class l felt like kissing brother's girl friend Catherine.
它是相当常见的，在这个年龄有这样的感觉。
lt's quite common to have such feeling in that age.
但凯瑟琳没有同意。
But Catherine didn't agree.
升生气了，L强奸并杀害了凯瑟琳。
l got angry, l raped and killed Catherine.
不仅如此，我弟弟的儿子约翰尼，
Not only that my brother's son Johnny,
我抓住他沉迷于毒品和女孩，并把他变成了'无情'约翰尼。
l got him addicted to drugs and girls and turned him into 'Ruthless' Johnny.
我嫂嫂前来了解。
My sister-in-law came to know about this.
别无选择，
Left with no choice,
我的妹妹在法律玛丽升浇上汽油烧她活着，
l doused my sister-in-law Mary with petrol and burnt her alive,
创建它就像一个火灾事故的发生。
and created it like a fire accident.
因此，L去教堂，神对我的犯罪事实供认不讳，
So, l went to church and confessed about my crime to God,
父亲是谁，你来之前听到的一切，
Father who was there before you came heard everything,
升生气了，升举行他的头发，把他拉出来，
l got angry, l held him by hair and pulled him out,
升印在他的脖子，勒死了他死刑。
l stamped on his neck and strangled him to death.
我已经决定，没有一个人知道真相，必须是活着的。
l've decided no one who knows the truth must be alive.
升所做的这一切吓得我哥哥维克多。
l had done all this scared of my brother Victor.
只有一个人在这个世界的爱和恐惧升！
There's only one man l love and fear in this world!
Baadshah杀了他，给我留下了一个孤儿。
Baadshah killed him and left me as an orphan.
我现在没有任何人，谁升？
l don't have anyone now, whom should l live for?
升必须活杀Baadshah的。
l must live to kill Baadshah.
你哥哥死了，没有履行杀害Baadshah的他的愿望。
Your brother died without fulfilling his wish of killing Baadshah.
此后，我们的共同目标是Baadshah。
Hereafter our common target is Baadshah.
Shift键立即装箱印度的。
Shift the container immediately to lndia.
香港港
Port of Hong Kong
你给一个休克没有透露关于此操作，直到最后一分钟。
You gave a shock by not revealing about this operation till last minute.
我不具有任何其他的选择。
l don't have any other choice.
你的工作苦行僧BHAI？
Are you working for Sadhu Bhai?
博纳亚阿迪，你救了容器，并做了我大忙。
Adhi, you saved the container and did a great favour to me.
能让自己部门认为Baadshah杀害警察和容器。
Make your department believe that Baadshah killed the police and took the container.
巴伊，，不止是取景Baadshah，我们一个机会去完成他。
Bhai, notjust framing Baadshah, we've a chance to finish him.
这是什么，儿子？ 你不给我打电话了2天。
What's this, son? You didn't call me for 2 days.
我有点忙。
l'm little busy.
在忙些什么，儿子？ 我会非常想念你。
What busy, son? l'm missing you very much.
当你回来了，儿子？
When are you coming back, son?
我是这里几乎完成了，母亲。 很快，我会再回到那里。
l'm almost done here, mother. Very soon l'll be back there.
我也爱你，亲爱的。 要小心。
Love you too, dear. Be careful.
你爸爸是我的儿子！
Your papa is with me, son!
来吧！
Come!
你困惑知道怎么升绑架你爸从你的地方吗？
Are you confused to know how l kidnapped your dad from your place?
朋友！
Friend!
为什么呢？
Why?
我会杀了你的父亲在你的眼前。
l'll kill your father right before your eyes.
获取Baadshah的父亲！
Get Baadshah's father!
lftiger是在细胞内，即使孩子们可以用它玩。
lftiger is inside the cell, even kids can play with it.
当它出来，它开始进入竞技场打猎！
When it comes out into the arena, it begins to hunt!
不止是香港警方，印度n警方也照顾你。
Notjust Hong Kong police, lndian police is also after you.
您照顾P我的爸爸，还有每一个问题的解决方案，
You take care p my dad, there's a solution to every problem,
我会找到解决的办法！
l'll find the solution!
是ACP博纳亚阿迪的摩尔部门谁苦行僧BHAI的工作？
Was ACP Adhi the mole in department who worked for Sadhu Bhai?
他告诉有关Baadshah杀害警察的谎言，是对他不利的证据。
The lie he told about Baadshah killing police is evidence against him.
我删除一些歹徒，在列表中您的指示。
l've erased a number of gangsters in the list on your instructions.
之前升了我的最终目标苦行僧BHAI
Before l reached my final target Sadhu Bhai,
我已经成为一个犯罪因为ofAdhi的背叛。
l've become a criminal because ofAdhi's betrayal.
l可以相信你，但你怎么能部门相信它吗？
l can believe you but how can you make the department believe it?
此外，博纳亚阿迪要嫁给我的侄女，
Moreover Adhi is going to marry my niece,
参与也是结束，
engagement is also over,
我的姐夫是海得拉巴处长，
my brother-in-law is Commissioner of Hyderabad,
我们家族世仇，
we've a family feud,
l可以不告诉关于博纳亚阿迪的，并让他相信，
l can't tell about Adhi and make him believe it,
但我们绝不能饶恕他。
but we mustn't spare him,
他背叛了我的部门，他毁了我侄女的生命。
he betrayed my department, he's out to ruin my niece's life.
我们只有一个赶上源博纳亚阿迪苦行僧BHAI的。
We've only one source Adhi to catch Sadhu Bhai.
他用博纳亚阿迪让我们，我们必须使用博纳亚阿迪得到他。
He used Adhi to get us, we must use Adhi to get him.
并保存你的侄女也从博纳亚阿迪。 但是，怎么样？
And save your niece also from Adhi. But how?
L'VE的计划，先生。
l've a plan, sir.
虽然你不是警察的男子，你冒着巨大的风险为目的，
Though you're not a police man, you're taking great risk for an aim,
我相信你一定会成功。
l'm sure you will succeed.
现在是你的侄女在哪里？
Where's your niece now?
Baadshah同一个目的来到ltaly，
Baadshah who came to ltaly with a purpose,
意外下滑爱萨拉萨。
unexpectedly fell in love with Janaki.
爸爸，姐姐的婚礼请柬都非常好。
Daddy, sister's wedding invitations are very good.
你的叔叔已经策划了盛大的婚礼。
Your uncle has planned a grand wedding.
妈咪叫，她想要得到的东西，对不对？
Mummy called, she wanted you to get something, right?
她会告诉她去结婚3个月前。
She will tell, she went to the marriage 3 months earlier.
L'做这里像一个女人的购物。
l'm doing the shopping like a woman here.
萨拉萨，带给我的记忆中，在2天内完成您的购物，
Janaki, that brings to my memory, finish your shopping in 2 days,
我们在2天离开印度的。
we're leaving to lndia in 2 days.
我们是如此兴奋，你的婚姻，你为什么如此沉闷，姐姐？
We're so excited about your marriage, why are you so dull, sister?
任何一个女孩子结婚接近离开亲人，也会感到难过。
Any girl would feel sad as marriage nears for leaving the loved ones.
什么急呢？ - 这么着急呢？ 房子着火了！
What's the hurry? - Hurry? The house is on fire!
萨拉萨的婚姻是固定的，你知道吗？
Janaki's marriage is fixed, you know that?
作为一个侧踢，如果L觉得这么多，多少为英雄，你会感觉如何？
As a side kick if l feel so much, as hero how much would you feel?
但是，我们能做些什么？
But what can we do?
他再次去自杀点？
Did he go to suicide point again?
拉玛也永远不会消失萨拉萨！
Rama can never go away from Janaki!
无论你骂，打，或嫁给我，你就是那个我爱...
Whether you scold, beat or marry me, you're the one l love...
如花萨拉萨... 你是如何害羞......
Flowery Janaki... How bashful you are...
跟我来到您的LN-法律的房子...
Come with me to your ln-law's house...
槟榔叶，坚果和钙是使口腔出现红色...
Betel leaf, nuts and calcium is to make mouth red...
已经美貌和青春，让你快乐......
l've beauty and youth to make you happy...
我会排挤你像蜂蜜从梳子美...
l'll squeeze out you beauty like honey from a comb...
像冷水下垫上... 你走近我，掐我的脸颊......
Like cool water under the mat... You came near me to pinch my cheek...
你轻轻地竖起像鱼骨...
You pricked gently like a fish bone...
我25岁的心脏不会去疯抢？
Won't my 25 year old heart go berserk?
在我的心里，你的调皮的眼睛已经敲响了钟...
Your mischievous eyes have rung the bell in my heart...
你我的羞怯消失...
You've made my shyness to vanish...
您是夜切匕首...
You're a dagger to cut the night...
你扑向我所有的力量...
You pounce on me with all the force...
整理好你的腰布，并带我到极乐世界与你一起...
Fold up your dhoti and take me along with you to world of bliss...
L'LL群你喜欢洪水破坝...
l'll swarm you like floods breaking the dam...
就像一个神奇的地雷炸毁了所有的秘密，看到你...
Like a magical landmine that blew up all the secrets on seeing you...
你为什么抢着，男孩？
Why are you rushing, boy?
你考虑过我的美丽...
You've taken over my beauty...
吐司OFTHE党...
Toast ofthe party...
能使用作为配菜，如果我是饿了吗？
Can l use as side dish if l'm hungry?
我没见过像你这样的人，我发誓......
l've not seen anyone like you, l swear...
好了轮廓分明的... 完美的......来吧，抱抱我......
Well chiseled... perfectly built...Come on, hug me...
瑞普我，吻我，我亲爱的...
Rip me, Kiss me, my dear...
不要点燃激情之火，充满欲望的眼睛......
Don't lit fire of passion with desire filled eyes...
命中像一辆飞驰的重型货车...
Hit like a speeding heavy lorry...
我欣赏，如果你把我紧紧拥抱......
l'll appreciate ifyou hug me tightly...
LS我的兄弟寺庙祭司修复婚姻，如果你说你爱她吗？
ls my brother temple priest to fix marriage ifyou say you love her?
他会杀了你相遇。
He'll kill you in encounter.
如果他杀死我爱他的女儿，
lf he kills me for loving his daughter,
你一直在欺骗他15岁，声称身为警务人员。
You've been cheating him for 15 years claiming as police officer.
与你，他会怎么做？
what would he do with you?
他会扑灭汽油和燃烧你还活着。
He'll douse you with petrol and burn you alive.
lnstead ofsomeone会虚心要求的人，
lnstead ofsomeone who would request humbly,
你为什么爱一个人，谁在威胁？
why did you love a man who threatens?
说服我的兄弟是不那么容易，因为勒索我。
Convincing my brother isn't as easy as blackmailing me.
在内部所有的男人都是警察。
All the men in house are police officers.
即使是牛奶的人，受雇人或响门铃，他必须是一个警察的男子。
Even milk man, servant or to ring door bell, he must be a police man.
我已经赢得了萨拉萨的爱，它不是很难赢得过你哥哥。
l've won Janaki's love, it's not difficult to win over your brother.
相信我。 - 是的叔叔。
Trust me. - Yes uncle.
LF拉玛饶命中，这是一个目标，确认！
lf Rama Rao hits, it's a goal, confirmed!
机票也证实。 - 一起。
Flight tickets are also confirmed. - All are together in it.
在这里做什么？ 让去印度！
What's there to do here? Let's go to lndia!
我们的货柜与2000公斤的RDX已达印度的。
Our container with 2000 kgs of RDX has reached lndia.
海得拉巴举行的世界首脑会议上20 ofthis月。
Hyderabad is hosting a world summit on 20th ofthis month.
岩石海得拉巴爆炸必须在同一天。
Blasts must rock Hyderabad on the same day.
炸弹必须在所有主要城市。
Bombs must go off in all major cities.
印度将成为一个恐怖分子国家在眼睛OFTHE世界，
lndia would become a terrorist country in the eyes ofthe world,
投资来印度将停止，
investments coming to lndia would stop,
卢比的价值会下跌，
rupee value will fall,
经济将陷入不可恢复的条件。
economy would fall into unrecoverable condition.
它为我们什么？ - 成千上万亿卢比。
What's in it for us? - Thousands of crores.
警报的所有的团伙为我们工作印度的。
Alert all the gangs working for us in lndia.
您太转移到印度的。 ACP博纳亚阿迪将您提供帮助。
You too shift to lndia. ACP Adhi will help you.
健身房的钟声响起来了！ 起床！
Gym bell is ringing! Get up!
健身房的钟声响起来了！ 起床！ - 健身房的钟声响起来了！ 起床！
Gym bell is ringing! Get up! - Gym bell is ringing! Get up!
这不是意大利，如果您把已故的兄弟在法律会杀了你。 起床！
This is not ltaly, ifyou get late brother-in-law would kill you. Get up!
这是不是像一个家，但私人部门的警察学院。
This isn't like a family home but a private branch of Police academy.
升私奔到了意大利无法承受这样的折磨。
l ran away to ltaly unable to bear this torture.
快速准备，一定要去哥哥来之前有。
Get ready quickly, must go before brother comes there.
即使电视肥皂剧周末有差距，但没有为你哥哥的纪律的差距。
Even TV soap operas have weekend gaps, but no gaps for your brother's discipline.
快速准备，如果您晚了，爸爸会杀了你。
Get ready quickly, ifyou get late, dad will kill you.
当牧师说，生活将在运行，如果l嫁给你，
When priest said life will be on run if l marry you,
我很开心，
l was very happy,
但没想到是这样的运行。
but l didn't expect the run to be like this.
快快起来。
Get up quickly.
lfyou来晚了，brotherwill杀了你。
lfyou come late, brotherwill kill you.
你的命运！
Your fate!
早上好兄弟，达到了深夜。
Good morning brother, reached late night.
这就是为什么我没有打扰你。
That's why l didn't disturb you.
它的日常工作??，尽管深夜抵达。
lt's routine to work out despite late night arrivals.
肚子鼓鼓的这是什么？ - 没有射击 - 射击？
What's this bulging belly? - No shootings.- Shooting?
升的意思没有太大的拍摄超时，要杀死罪犯，爸爸。
l mean not much of shoot outs to kill criminals, daddy.
L右，叔叔？ - 是的，亲爱的。
Am l right, uncle? - Yes dear.
的义大利黑手党??坐在家里担心Pilli的压力。
ltalian mafia is sitting in home fearing Pilli's pressure.
你已经证明了Pilli人，他永远是虎！
You've proved that a Pilli man is tiger where ever he is!
如何做的义大利警察功能？ - 他们总是在某些功能。
How do the ltalian police function? - They're always in some functions.
如果我不管理，我或许会遇到麻烦。
lf l don't manage, l may be in trouble.
升太想分享我的经验与所有ofyou
l too want to share my experience with all ofyou,
但妹夫还没来。 - 尚未。
but brother-in-law hasn't come yet. - Not yet.
早上好，姐夫。
Good morning, brother-in-law.
你在做什么不来健身房？
What were you doing without coming to gym?
氧水平已经回落的房子，所以升在KBR公园慢跑3轮。
Oxygen level has come down in house, so l jogged 3 rounds in KBR park.
什么几轮？ - 什么？ 慢跑轮。
What rounds? - What else? Jogging rounds.
奇怪，L在第一轮遇到Akkineni Nageshwara饶，
Strange, l met Akkineni Nageshwara Rao in the first round,
第二轮，升会见了国王龙树
second round, l met King Nagarjuna,
第三轮，柴坦尼亚跟我握了握手。
third round, Chaitanya shook hands with me.
所以，你是第四代3代的孩子。
So, you're a 4th generation kid to cover 3 generations.
我的脚！
My foot!
饶Nageshwara是在美国塔纳会议，
Nageshwara Rao is in America for Tana Conference,
龙树是在欧洲forfilm的拍摄像往常一样。
Nagarjuna is in Europe forfilm shoot as usual.
娜迦切塔尼亚是在Pollachi。
Naga Chaitanya is in Pollachi.
泰卢固语业如何才能做好，如果每个人都的竹笋出OFTHE状态？
How can Telugu industry do well if everyone shoots out ofthe state?
您必须改革没有泰卢固产业。 什么是你的体重？
You must reform not Telugu industry. What's your weight?
不应该是什么yourweight，叔叔问你的体重？
Not what yourweight should be, uncle's asking what's your weight?
什么水平新书胆固醇？ - 他希望！
What's the level ofyour cholesterol? - As much as he wants!
你能读你的裤子拉链上的名字不弯腰？
Can you read the name on your pant zip without bending?
非常困难，姐夫。 l可看不出来。
Very difficult, brother-in-law. l can't see it.
需要多长时间？ - 由于10年。
How long? - Since 10 years.
我未来的女婿说你的坏话。
My future son-in-law is talking bad about you.
他感觉不好，就像你在他的团队中有一个无用的人员。
He's feeling bad for having a useless officer like you in his team.
难道你不感觉不好，越来越受到大家的批评？
Aren't you feeling bad for getting criticized by everyone?
不要你的感情吗？
Don't you've any feelings?
饥饿是一种感觉，对不对？
Hunger too is a feeling, right?
不要总是像猪吃。 警务人员应该如何！
Don't always eat like a pig. How a police officer should be!
他一定是喜欢上了膛的枪。
He must be like a loaded gun.
你怎么样？ - 就像一个装货车。
How are you? - Like a loaded lorry.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
Moreoveryou太上火！
Moreoveryou get angry too!
母亲！ - 兄弟！
Mother! - Brother!
什么兄弟？ 你怎么能爱这个糟糕的男人？
What brother? How could you love this lousy man?
他不值得守望在这里，但我是为你容忍他。
He doesn't deserve to be watchman here but l'm tolerating him for you.
他甚至不能跑10米，但我运用影响力，让他为你lnspector。
He couldn't even run 10 metres but l used influence to make him lnspector for you.
看看他的脸！
Look at his face!
喜欢刮老猴子！
Like a shaven old monkey!
他是一个缩影谎言，懒惰，灾难，作弊，犯规！
He's an epitome of lies, laziness, disaster, cheating, foul!
LT的不必要的谈论他。
lt's unnecessary to talk about him.
一般人死于疾病，但他可能死于纪律。
Generally people die of disease but he may die for discipline.
去4轮马不停蹄的化合物附近账面Bunty躺在。
Go 4 rounds non-stop around the compound carrying Bunty for lying.
关注他！
Watch him!
4轮不停！ 上午升维杰亚瓦达Kodada的公交车？
4 rounds non-stop! Am l Vijayawada-Kodada bus?
是我的错，与她结婚，并成为内部女婿？
Was it my mistake to marry her and become in-house son-in-law?
右，妹夫。
Right, brother-in-law.
lfyou没有到了这家，忘了肚子，你会被饿死。
lfyou hadn't come to this house, forget about belly, you would be starving.
为什么寻找这样的lnstead，不与家人系统同步？
lnstead of looking like that, why don't you sync with family system?
LS你的伟大的王室同步与您的家人的传统？
ls yours great royal family to sync with your family tradition?
您的姓是什么？
What's your surname?
因为它是弱猫，如果你添加'SIMHA“（狮子）您的姓名，
Since it's weak cat, ifyou add 'Simha' (lion) to your name,
你真的可以成为狮子吗？
can you really become lions?
他为什么要操心我的身高和体重？
Why should he bother about my height and weight?
LS，他背着我？ 血淋淋的脏口！
ls he carrying me? Bloody dirty mouth!
你为什么滥用我的哥哥吗？
Why are you abusing my brother?
生气，如果l滥用你的兄弟，但是当他虐待我？
Getting angry if l abuse your brother, but when he abused me?
我阻止他，对不对？
l did stop him, right?
几乎当他做，他说，母亲和你说哥哥合唱。
Almost when he's done with, he says mother and you say brother in chorus.
他在中国像一头公牛去疯抢。
He goes berserk like a bull in china.
L'没有傻到知道你是否阻止他或惹他。
l'm not foolish enough to know whether you're stopping him or provoking him.
是谁呢？
Who is it?
妹夫！
Brother-in-law!
什么做的惩罚几轮讨论，但无？
What's the discussion without doing the punishment rounds?
我是教他们如何警务人员不应该！
l'm teaching them how a police officer shouldn't be!
无需讲座，只要你就够了。
No need of lectures for it, simply showing you is enough.
lfthere邀请函，邀请这么多的错误VLP部门，
lfthere are so many mistakes in invitations to invite VlP's in the department,
在这样一个盛大的婚姻，有多少你会犯更多的错误？
how many more mistakes would you commit in such a grand marriage?
为什么每个人都沉默着？
Why is everyone silent?
关于婚礼请柬...... - 难道他不喜欢它吗？
About wedding invitations... - Didn't he like it?
他喜欢，他想知道谁得到它印。
He liked it, he wants to know who got it printed.
难道你不告诉他呢？ 你不会告诉他这样的事情。
Didn't you tell him? You won't tell him such things.
我抓住它打印出来，姐夫。
l got it printed, brother-in-law.
因此，它是你的创作，对不对？
So, it was your creation, right?
是的，颜色，文字，增删，一切都是我的工作。
Yes, colour, words, additions and deletions, everything is my work.
哪里是的标题医生之前，我的名字吗？
Where's the title doctor before my name?
我的度在哪里？ - 我告诉他们将其删除。
Where are my degrees? - l told them to remove it.
它看起来像一些性病专家。
lt looks like some sex specialist.
<看上去家常。 这就是为什么我删除了所有垃圾。
lt looks homely. That's why l removed all that trash.
你是谁删除的？
Who are you to remove that?
Pilli APPA饶我父亲辛勤工作了25年之久，
My father Pilli Appa Rao toiled for 25 long years,
他骑自行车我的方式来教育，
he bicycled my way to education,
这些都是我的辛勤工作赚取度升，
those are the degrees l earned with my hard work,
你怎么知道它的价值吗？
how would you know the value of it?
你没出息。 无用的，可怜的，流氓！
You're good for nothing. Useless, pathetic, rogue!
母亲！ - 兄弟！
Mother! - Brother!
什么兄弟？
What brother?
L'总署接纳了他，虽然他没有对你中间。
l'd accepted him though he failed intermediate for you.
我抓住他的警察的工作适合你，虽然他不能拼写程度。
l got him police job for you though he can't spell degree.
你来吧。
Come.
他这样的反应缺失程度的邀请卡。
He reacted like this for missing degrees in the invitation card.
你想改变新郎。 LS这可能吗？
You want to change the groom. ls it possible?
它一定会发生，叔叔。 升信任拉玛饶！
lt will surely happen, uncle. l trust Rama Rao!
我文化分工的新掌门人。
l'm the new head of cultural division.
我们过去3年每年庆祝一天Lahari度假村。
We've been celebrating annual day in Lahari resorts for the past 3 years.
我们决定庆祝在Pragathi度假村，今年改变。
We've decided to celebrate in Pragathi resorts this year for a change.
对于变化，我们也决定一样。
For a change we too decided the same.
你不会理会我们的感情，如果你决定？
Won't you bother about our feelings ifyou decide?
你不会给我们的员工的感受价值？
Won't you give value to the feelings of our employees?
你必须这样做仅Pragathi度假村！
You must do it in Pragathi resorts only!
这是什么？ 我们说，我们只有已经预订了。
What's this? We said we've booked there only.
lfyou，然后取消它。
lfyou had, then cancel it.
您是否担心失去你的佣金？
Are you worried about losing your commission?
你走了后赔钱的业务？
Have you gone made after losing money in business?
你为什么过火，即使我们同意了吗？
Why do you overact even after we agreed?
这是好事，我不紧张自己ifyou'd接受，对不对？
This is good, l wouldn't strain myself ifyou'd accepted it earlier, right?
叔叔，他有点难以听到。 - 明白了吗？
Uncle, he's little hard to hear. - Got it?
停止讨论，并给予付款细节。
Stop discussion and give payment details.
去年是Rs.4万卢比，现在价格已经涨了，
Last year it was Rs.4 lakhs, now prices have gone up,
夫人说，的价格是Rs.5万卢比。
madam says the price is Rs.5 lakhs.
卢比万卢比？ LT的太多。 Rs.8万卢比对我来说是好的。
Rs.10 lakhs? lt's too much. Rs.8 lakhs is okay to me.
升认为他的缺陷是我们有好处。
l think his defect is benefit to us.
你为什么你们之间的讨论吗？ 告诉我你的价格。
Why are you discussing among yourselves? Tell me your price.
（LF Rs.8万卢比）是好的，给你，那么它也没关系。
lf Rs.8 lakhs is okay to you, then it's okay to us also.
什么好吗？ - 问候夫人。
What okay? - Greetings madam.
我们的付款是Rs.5万卢比！
Our payment is Rs.5 lakhs!
我是你的诚实打动交易敲定后，给予贴息。
l'm impressed with your honesty to give discount after deal is finalized.
到了晚上，我提前发送。
l'll send the advance by evening.
再见夫人。 - 再见。
Bye madam. - Bye.
你永远不会改变，人们尝试挤压最大客户。
You'll never change, people try to squeeze maximum from customers.
你尝试降低价格。
and you try to reduce the price.
不要欺骗那些相信你的人，哥。
Never cheat those who trust you, brother.
说好了，妈妈。
Well said, mother.
这是什么surprize访问？
What's this surprize visit?
我是在这里给你一个突如其来的妈妈。
l'm here to give you a surprize, mom.
你怎么样？ - 精细。
How are you doing? - Fine.
他是谁？ - 我的朋友，他会和我们呆在一起。
Who is he? - My friend, he'll stay with us.
梳洗，让我们吃午饭。
Freshen up, let's have lunch.
新业务？ 那是什么？
New business? What's that?
我们没有经验。
We don't have experience in it.
事件管理，你现在正在做什么？
What's event management that you're doing now?
装饰根据不同的场合，根据自己的口味的晚餐，
Decorate according to the occasion, dinners according to their tastes,
文化娱乐节目。
cultural programs for entertainment.
lfyou结合一切，做一次，这是举行婚礼。
lfyou combine everything and do it for one occasion, that's wedding.
他们不花各方微薄，但对于婚姻，他们会花上亿卢比。
They don't spend pittance for parties but for marriage they'll spend crores.
但谁给我们的信任和婚姻合同吗？
But who would trust and give us marriage contract?
lfwe取得他们的信任，他们就会给。
lfwe gain their trust, they'll give.
专员，你买传统jewellary这里为您的所有功能。
Commissioner, you traditionally buy jewellary here for all your functions.
随着信心我是告诉你这个婚礼策划是正确的选择。
With that confidence l'm telling you this wedding planner is the right choice.
既然你推荐他，我会试探他在我的风格。
Since you recommend him, l'll test him in my style.
男孩在哪里？
Where's the boy?
在这里，他来了。
Here he comes.
赛斯的问候！ - 请坐下。
Greetings Seth! - Please sit down.
你为什么给我打电话？ - 我会告诉你，
Why did you call me? - l'll tell you,
我的名字是Subrahmanyam。 专员办公室科员。
my name is Subrahmanyam. Section officer in Commissioner's office.
LS呢？
ls it?
专员已计划他女儿的婚事很隆重。
Commissioner has planned his daughter's marriage very grandly.
他给了我这个责任。
He has given me that responsibility.
塞斯告诉我，你，ifwe达成谅解，
Seth told me about you, ifwe come to an understanding,
这将是我和你太有利。 - 这是怎么回事？
it'll be beneficial to you and me too.- How is that?
如果的婚姻殿堂租金是10卢比万卢比，
lf marriage hall rent is Rs.10 lakhs,
我们会引述卢比万卢比，让分享利润50-50！
we'll quote as Rs.20 lakhs, let's share the profit 50-50!
lffood是每盘1000卢比，我们将引用为2000卢比每盘。
lffood is Rs.1000 per plate, we'll quote it as Rs.2000 per plate.
让分享50-50！
Let's share it 50-50!
装修lfflower Rs.5万卢比，让我们引用它作为卢比万卢比，
lfflower decoration is Rs.5 lakhs, let's quote it as Rs.10 lakhs,
让应占50-50！
Let's share 50-50!
让安排汗Mumaith的舞蹈在sangeeth程序，
Let's arrange Mumaith Khan's dance in sangeeth program,
我们会付给她10卢比万卢比，并声称Rs.25万卢比。
we'll pay her Rs.10 lakhs and claim Rs.25 lakhs.
让应占50-50！ 你说什么？
Let's share 50-50! What do you say?
我会击败你带拖鞋！
l'll beat you with slippers!
起床的人！
Get up man!
你们将采取专员专员本人，血腥的犯罪。
Will you take commissioner from Commissioner himself, bloody criminal.
你知不知道婚姻是什么？
Do you know what marriage is?
整个庆祝活动必须记录在心里，而不是在CD！
Entire celebration must be recorded in heart not on CD!
婚姻树冠像寺庙是神圣的！
Marriage canopy is sacred like temple!
你知道为什么结婚宴席总是优秀？
Do you know why marriage feast is always excellent?
为了确保客人吃得好，祝福心！
To ensure guests eat well and bless with heart!
你会从中拿提成？ 该死的骗子！
Will you take commission from it? Bloody crook!
我是骂你，你笑什么？
l'm scolding you and are you laughing?
你安排了Mumaith汗的舞蹈sangeeth的吗？
Will you arrange Mumaith Khan's dance in sangeeth?
LS其婚姻或录音舞吗？
ls it marriage or recording dance?
赛斯，呼叫专员，让我们来收拾他。
Seth, call Commissioner, let's fix him.
没有需要，他的专员。
No need, he's Commissioner.
LS他专员...
ls he Commissioner...
升先生犯了一个错误。 - 你有没有做过什么错事。
l made a mistake sir. - You haven't done anything wrong.
这是你的性格，我喜欢它。
That's your character, l like it.
赛斯，你提出了一个很好的男孩。
Seth, you've suggested a good boy.
我是给他的婚姻合同。
l'm giving the marriage contract to him.
不紧张，因为我专员，
Don't get nervous because l'm Commissioner,
服务好，赚好名字。 - 好吧，先生。
serve well and earn good name. - Okay sir.
赛斯将讨论其他细节。
Seth will discuss other details.
再见。 - 好吧，先生。
Bye. - Okay sir.
非常感谢你，叔叔。
Thank you very much, uncle.
我采取这种风险，因为OFTHE信任L'VE对你和你母亲。
l've taken this risk because ofthe trust l've on you and your mother.
没有请让UPS在婚姻。 - 这段婚姻永远不会发生。
No let ups in marriage please. - This marriage will never happen.
升意味着这门亲事通常不会发生。
l mean this marriage will not happen ordinarily.
lt'll是疯狂的！
lt'll be the craziest!
欢迎兄弟！ - 欢迎妹夫。
Welcome brother! - Welcome brother-in-law.
你的家是已经闪耀着婚姻的光芒！
Already your home is shining with marriage glow!
有人曾炸毁了一个炸弹！ 是谁呢？
Someone has blown up a bomb! Who is it?
他的婚礼策划师。 他的名字是拉玛饶。
He's the wedding planner. His name is Rama Rao.
问候叔叔。
Greetings uncle.
婚姻是10天的日子，你为什么开始的庆祝活动？
Marriage is 10 days away, why have you started the celebrations?
婚姻专员的房子，必须令人兴奋的！
Marriage in Commissioner's house must be mind blowing!
你还没有见过最好的，叔叔。
You haven't yet seen the best, uncle.
还有更多的商店！
There's much more in store!
LS，他的新郎？ 他很帅气！
ls he the groom? He's very handsome!
叔叔，他一直隐藏的六个包里面，不知道他还有什么躲在里面呢？
Uncle, he has hidden s six pack inside, don't know what else he's hiding inside?
不要生气，哥们！ 只是为了好玩。
Don't get angry, buddy! Just for fun.
婚姻是乐趣！ 你说什么？
Marriage is fun! What do you say?
请进来，让坐在里面和讨论，妹夫。
Please come in, let's sit inside and discuss, brother-in-law.
这突如其来的会议讨论，被称为
This sudden meeting has been called to discuss,
我们的大师Sampurnandha斯瓦米已经发现新郎的占星中的缺陷。
our Guru Sampurnandha Swamiji has found a defect in groom's horoscope.
身体的缺陷有医药，占星，有什么补救措施吗？
Defect in body has medicine, what's the remedy for horoscope?
解决方案是水！
Solution is water!
笨蛋！ 它的不是一般的或矿物，它是永恒的！
Fool! lt's not general or mineral, it's eternal!
这锅包含圣水收集所有神圣的河流，
This pot which contains holy water collected from all holy rivers,
新娘必须站在正北方向，并给它到新郎的南部手。
bride must stand in north direction and give it to groom's southern hands.
我们应该去东部和洒它所有的方式吗？
Should we go east and sprinkle it all the way?
，这圣洁的水奉献圣洁的罗勒植物。
No, consecrate holy Basil plant with this holy water.
在家里，我们没有罗勒或茉莉花植物。
We don't have basil or jasmine plants in home.
lfyou不具备的，它是在市场上，
lfyou don't have, it's available in market,
我们可以买一个，供奉在家里。 你说什么，斯瓦米？
we can buy one and consecrate it in home. What do you say, Swami?
时间正在流逝，叫新娘。
Time is elapsing, call the bride.
拿去吧，把它交给新郎。
Take it, give it to the groom.
不要给它任何人或让它掉下来，直到你到达家里。
Don't give it to anyone or let it fall down till you reach home.
如果它下降？ - 你的儿子就完了。
lf it falls? - Your son will be finished.
闭嘴，牧师！ 你太迷信。
Shut up, priest! You're too superstitious.
LS他的孩子扔了下来？
ls he kid to throw it down?
当高级牧师修复婚姻，没有什么能阻止它。
When senior priest fixes the marriage, nothing can stop it.
叔叔是成功的一半死了，他做了什么，
Uncle is half dead for what he has done,
如果愤怒地看到，他可能真的死。
ifyou see angrily he may really die.
叔叔大肆做到这一点吗？
Did uncle do it wantonly?
你说得对，我这样匆忙......
You're right, l did like this in haste...
这婚姻是这两我们的合同，
This marriage is notjust a contract for us,
我们认为，作为一个函数在我们的家。
we consider it as a function in our home.
离开了我的男孩和享受！
Leave everything to my boys and enjoy!
谢谢你这么多，我们已经安排了房子为他们的逗留。
Thank you so much, we've arranged out house for their stay.
她是我的女儿萨拉萨，新娘。 拉姆的母亲。
She's my daughter Janaki, the bride. Ram's mother.
阿姨的问候。 - 亲爱的问候。
Greetings aunty. - Greetings dear.
你很漂亮。
You're very beautiful.
当你带回家一个女孩喜欢她，拉姆？
When are you bringing home a girl like her, Ram?
如果你真的喜欢她，让她到我们家，母亲。
ifyou really like her, let's take her to our home, mother.
l表示，它的乐趣，婚姻意味着乐趣！
l said it for fun, marriage means fun!
看着你的游戏计划，L觉得我们一定会取胜。
Watching your game plan, l feel we'll surely win.
但球是不是你的手来启动它。
But the ball isn't your hands to start it.
lfwe得到大家到地面，球会来我的手。
lfwe get everyone to ground, ball will come to my hand.
已经对你的信心。
l've full faith in you.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
你的新娘... - 不要惊慌。
You're with bride... - Don't panic.
我们不是在这里进行的婚姻，但阻止它。
We're not here to conduct marriage but to stop it.
你在说什么？ - 是的，叔叔。
What are you saying? - Yes, uncle.
让我们停止这种婚姻和萨拉萨到我们家媳妇。
Let's stop this marriage and take Janaki to our home as daughter-in-law.
你会采取什么你？
What will you take with you?
升的意思是，我们在谈论什么，以及如何从这里拿东西？
l mean we're discussing about what and how to take things from here?
lsn't呢？ - 停止矫枉过正，不能耐受。
lsn't it? - Stop overacting, can't tolerate it.
你说你会来印度的太到家。
You said you'd come to lndia and reached home too.
我哥哥从来不信任任何人，
My brother who never trusts anyone,
他已经对你进行婚姻的全部责任。
he has given entire responsibility of conducting marriage on you.
他是否知道你的事吗？ - 他知道，他也是我们的党。
Does he know your matter? - He knows, he's also our party.
什么样的党？ - Sangeeth党。
What party? - Sangeeth party.
我们正在讨论关于sangeeth党。 你也可以参加。
We're discussing about sangeeth party. You too can participate.
不要用力太多的婚姻不会发生。
Don't strain too much for a marriage that won't happen.
你打算如何阻止这门亲事呢？
How are you planning to stop this marriage?
你的意思是她太... - 她知道的一切。
You mean she too... - She knows everything.
她也是我们党。
She too is our party.
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
您也都知道ofeverything的，我们正在讨论关于他的计划，
You too are aware ofeverything, we're discussing about his plan,
告诉她我们要带走他们的女儿吗？
tell her how we're going to take away their daughter?
带走我的女儿？
Take away my daughter?
我们正在讨论有关如何接新娘婚姻的殿堂。
We're discussing about how to take the bride to marriage hall.
她不知道吗？
Doesn't she know?
什么？ - 他说，难道你不知道，这也？
What? - He says don't you know this also?
叔叔，这是我们日常工作的一部分，怎么会知道呢？
Uncle, it's part of our daily duty, how would she know it?
她会感到兴奋，如果它是纱丽选择！
She would get excited if it's sari selections!
说得好。
Well said.
纱丽都来自Kanchi，来选择。
Saris have come from Kanchi, come and select.
你也来。 - ...去...
You too come. - Go...go...
叔叔，你会毁了整个计划，你的愚蠢。
Uncle, you'd have ruined entire plan with your foolishness.
怎么办呢？
What to do?
L'迷茫像国家政治不知道谁是属于哪一方！
l'm confused like state politics don't know who belongs to which party!
你给我一个名单，我心脏。
You give me a list, l'll by heart it.
我们的下一步行动是什么？
What's our next move?
我们需要一个替罪羊，我们的下一步行动。 - 替罪羊？
We need a scapegoat for our next move. - Scapegoat?
是的，先生，我已经进入了家庭，按计划。
Yes sir, l've entered the home as per the plan.
需要一个替罪羊来阻止这种婚姻和陷阱博纳亚阿迪的。
l need a scapegoat to stop this marriage and trap Adhi.
我抓住它，但谁是替罪羊？
l got it, but who is that scapegoat?
你是人类还是野兽？
Are you human or beast?
我告诉你到逮捕潘杜Punjagutta，请你为什么要逮捕他的儿子？
l told you to arrest Punjagutta Pandu, why did you arrest his son?
他是在地下，我抓住他的儿子在学校的场地。
He's underground and l got his son in school ground.
我以为，如果L逮捕他，他会出来。
l thought if l arrest him, he would come out.
将收取2级的孩子强奸？
For that will you charge a class 2 kid with rape?
2级的孩子吗？
Class 2 kid?
母亲！ - 兄弟！
Mother! - Brother!
什么兄弟？
What brother?
他像野猪吃六次。 他不能用他的大脑呢？
He eats six times like a wild boar. can't he use his brain?
LT的死比活这样。
lt's better to die than live like this.
LS你的生命值得活下去？ 你怎么会爱上这样一个男人？
ls your life worth living? How could you love such a man?
没用的，愚蠢的，败家子，白痴...
Useless, stupid, wastrel, idiot...
侄子，他可能真的自杀。
Nephew, he may really kill himself.
你瞎胡闹！
You bloody fool!
我一个人，这就是为什么我喝。
l'm a human, that's why l'm drinking.
你是一个恶魔，这就是为什么你每天喝我的血。
You're a demon, that's why you drink my blood every day.
你油炸深深吃了我。
You're frying deeply and eating me.
如果神是存在的，我也弄了一天！
lf God is there, l'll also get a day!
L'LL私刑你喜欢一个臭虫。 这是我的愿望......我的目标......
l'll lynch you like a bedbug. That's my wish...my aim...
叔叔，让接手这个垫背的梦想项目。 你来吧。
Uncle, let's take over this scapegoat's dream project. Come.
他站起身来！
He got up!
告诉你不要把它在这里，直到婚姻是吗？
Did l tell you not to bring it here till marriage is over?
你为什么把它在这里？ - 号。
Why did you bring it here? - No..
什么没有？ 它是如何危险ifsomeone看到它吗？
What no? How danger it is ifsomeone sees it?
你在这里做什么？ 否则巫术？
What are you doing here? Doing voodoo?
这是什么照明？ 这把椅子是什么？
What's this lighting? What's this chair?
我求求你，叔叔，请不要喊。
l beg you, uncle, please don't shout.
这是梦想中的机器没有椅子。
This is dream machine not a chair.
我知道时光机，洗衣机，这是什么梦机器？
l know washing machine, time machine, what's this dream machine?
梦机器，这使得我们的梦想成真。
Dream machine is that which makes our dream come true.
叔叔在他的生活中，每个人都有一个小人。
Uncle, every man has a villain in his life.
他会被折磨我们。 我们不能伤害他，无论如何。
He would be torturing us. We can't harm him in anyway.
抑制将导致我们陷入萧条。
The suppression will lead us into depression.
造成紧张和恼火，
that creates tension and we get irritated,
它在我们的身体产生震动，
it generates vibrations in our body,
心将被封锁和心灵将得到来袭，
heart will get blocked and mind will get struck,
大脑会得到中风！ - 接下来是什么？
brain will get the stroke! - What next?
接下来是什么？ 埋葬，正确的男生吗？ - 是的。
What next? Burial, right boys? - Yes.
美国人认为提前许多这样死亡，并发现这台机器，
Americans thought advance about many dying like this and found this machine,
他们制作了一部电影在英语'lnception促进，叔叔！
they made a film in English 'lnception' to promote this, uncle!
它被冠以泰卢固语呢？ 叫什么名字？ - 'Arambam・（lnception）
lt was dubbed in Telugu too? What was the name? - 'Arambam' (lnception)
右，中国复制这种想法，这两份。
Right, Chinese copied this idea and made this duplicate.
高兴我们的婚姻计划，他提出与此有关。
happy with our marriage plans and he presented us with this.
我们可以主宰折磨我们的人的梦想和快乐的人。
We can dominate people who torture us in dream and be happy.
将适合身体和我们的生活会得到保存。
Body will be fit and our life would get saved.
得到它，叔叔？
Got it, uncle?
得到它，我想坐在这台机器上，并进入梦想世界。
Got it, l want to sit on this machine and enter dream world.
你为什么不想去，叔叔？
Why do you want to go, uncle?
每个人都人都有自己的悲伤故事。
Everyone one has his own tales of sorrow.
l我得到的折磨我的妹夫，脑中风。
l my get that brain stroke for the torture of my brother-in-law.
你面对什么困难！
What a difficulty you're facing!
所以，让mejoin你的俱乐部。
So, let mejoin your club.
好吧，但也有几个条件。 - 它们是什么？
Okay but there are few conditions. - What are they?
当你进入梦想，现实生活中的人物也来了，
When you enter dream, real life characters too come,
你不能告诉他们，你是在梦中！
you mustn't tell them that you're in dream!
如果告诉，该怎么办？ - 你会死在梦中。
What if l tell? - You'd die in dream.
所以，whateveryou想分享你的梦想，
So, whateveryou want to share about your dream,
它必须只与俱乐部的成员。
it must with club members only.
一个更重要的事情，叔叔。
One more important thing, uncle.
10分钟，在梦中是等于10天在现实生活中。
10 minutes in dream is equal to 10 days in real life.
如果你，出来OFTHE梦想？
lf l want to come out ofthe dream?
只要唱这不久，起床起床...我的王......
Just sing this soon, get up...get up...my King...
现在升了你。 请带我迅速的梦想。
Now l got you. Please take me to dream quickly.
好吧，叔叔，您必须是英雄新书的梦想。
Okay uncle, you must be the hero ofyour dream.
健身房的钟声响起，赶紧爬起来。
Gym bell has rung, get up quickly.
饮料所有的夜晚和我弟弟被斥责。
Drinks all the night and gets chided by my brother.
无耻的男人！ 不知道什么时候他会得到有意义吗？
Shameless man! Don't know when would he get sense?
她去健身房，钟鸣响。
She's going to gym, bell is ringing there.
一切是家常便饭。 但拉玛饶说自己的梦想。
Everything is routine. But Rama Rao said its dream.
欢迎...欢迎光临！
Welcome...welcome!
您是......？
You are...?
LS您拉玛？ 像NTR actjust！
ls it you Rama? You actjust like NTR!
你有没有看到，叔叔！ 能行动多么伟大！
You haven't seen much, uncle! How great can l act!
你可以看到它在未来和超越！
You can see it in future and beyond that!
这没关系！ 这是怎么呢？
That's okay! What's all this?
梦想！ 叔叔，你现在是在梦中。
Dream! Uncle, you're in dream now.
我们已经进入了你的梦想。
We've entered your dream.
你说的梦想，但像杜宾喊我妹夫。
You say dream but my brother-in-law is shouting like a Doberman.
疯狂的叔叔！ 为什么你进入梦想？
Mad uncle! Why did you enter dream?
在现实生活中的人采取报复。
To take revenge on people in real life.
谁是小人？ - 他的弟弟在的法律Jaikrishna SIMHA！
Who is the villain? - His brother-in-law Jaikrishna Simha!
他打电话给你，你应该怎么做，叔叔？
He's calling you, what should you do, uncle?
我抓住它，l必须采取的报复。 这是我的愿望，目的...
l got it, l must take revenge. That's my wish, aim...
你还在等什么？ 胜利可能是你的！
What are you waiting for? May victory be yours!
我是来了！
l'm coming!
他和他的血腥纪律！
He and his bloody discipline!
你应该已经跑过来，你为什么像一个英雄吗？
You should've come running, why are you coming like a hero?
现在的时间是什么？ - 谁知道呢？ 你想检查自己。
What's the time now? - Who knows? it you want check yourself.
你为什么要问我？
Why are you asking me?
这是什么语言和身体语言？
What's this language and body language?
改变了......一切都改变了。
Changed...everything is changed.
天升看着在厨房当饿了或酒吧当升渴，
Days l looked at kitchen when hungry or bar when l was thirsty is over,
年升哭在这所房子里的食物和饮料。
For years l cried for food and drinks in this house.
升哭了好宁静的睡眠。
l cried for good peaceful sleep.
现在，我的眼睛都在燃烧，如果有人胆敢阻止我......
Now my eyes are burning, if anyone dares stop me...
他们会得到化为灰烬！
They would get reduced to ashes!
无论是你来拼orwar的，
Whether you come for fight orwar,
无论您是前来与流氓或打手，
whether you come with hooligans or goons,
您是否只身来到整个家庭orwith，
whether you come alone orwith entire family,
如果你敢对我，我暗恋你喜欢酸辣酱！
ifyou dare taken on me, l'll crush you like chutney!
嚣张什么？ 你想要就要挨打？
What's that arrogance? You want to get beaten up?
你竟敢打我的妹妹！
How dare you beat my sister!
我揍你！ - 你打我？
l'll beat you also! - Will you beat me?
离开我，我会咬你的碎片。
Leave me, l'll bite you to pieces.
L'LL枪你失望。
l'll gun you down.
离开我离开我......
Leave me...leave me...
这是什么战斗在梦中也，叔叔？
What's this fight in dream also, uncle?
升进入梦想报复他，对不对？
l entered dream to take revenge on him, right?
什么踢ifyou直接去到高潮？
What's the kick ifyou go to climax directly?
你给了他一搏，对不对？ 去喝上一杯。
You gave him a stroke, right? Go and have a drink.
它会不会被罚款喝一天的时间。
lt won't be fine to drink in day time.
梦有没有白天还是黑夜。 - 你说的那样！
Dream has no day or night. - You say like that!
离开我离开我......
Leave me...leave me...
他发生了什么事？ 为什么他的行为像疯狗一样吗？
What happened to him? Why is he behaving like a mad dog?
L'也吓坏了，兄弟。 - 有什么可怕的。
l'm also scared, brother. - There's nothing to fear.
他曾恐吓我们，你说什么好怕的。
He has terrorised us, you say nothing to fear.
我处理类似的病人，所以我知道它。
l've handled a similar patient, so l know it.
LT的一种心理障碍。
lt's a psychological disorder.
LT创造的抑郁症由于抑制了一场革命！
lt's a revolution created by depression due to suppression!
lfwe没有打扰他们，让他们一个星期，
lfwe leave them for a week without bothering about them,
他们会趋于正常。 - 如果我们做什么呢？
they'll become normal. - What ifwe don't?
他们将不会放过任何人。
They'll not spare anyone.
他们会发疯，人可能咬脖子。
They'll go mad and may bite necks of people.
他怎么能赶上这样一种危险的疾病呢？
How could he catch such a dangerous disease?
LT超过统治造成的问题。
lt's the problem created by over domination.
是兄弟，升太被受到抑制你的统治。
Yes brother, l too got affected by suppression by your domination.
是的，L也陷入抑郁症。
Yes, l too fell into depression.
是兄弟，L也迷路了一阵骚动。
Yes brother, l too got lost in commotion.
升也得到了那些革命思想。
l too got those revolution thoughts.
是爸爸，人就会失去平衡像球ifthere的压力太大。
Yes daddy, man will lose balance like ball ifthere's too much pressure.
等待亲爱的。 你和你那该死的球理论。
Wait dear. You and your damn ball theory.
我了解，你认为我的学科作为我的统治。
l've understood that you consider my discipline as my domination.
所以，只要你喜欢，直到萨拉萨的婚姻。
So, be as you like till Janaki's marriage.
让我们结婚后会做出新的更简单的规则。
Let's have a meeting after marriage and make new easier rules.
每个人都会与疾病的影响已经得到了，如果L进一步推迟。
Everyone would've got affected with that disease if l had delayed further.
保持控制之下，直到这个婚姻是我妹夫。
Keep my brother-in-law under control till this marriage is over.
把他交给我，照顾其他的事情。
Leave him to me, take care of other things.
对话交付，叔叔！
What a dialogue delivery, uncle!
相信我，你的兄弟在法律润湿了他的裤子 - 是的，叔叔。
Trust me, your brother-in-law wetted his pants!- Yes, uncle.
我妹夫会不记得这个afterwaking，对不对？
My brother-in-law won't remember this afterwaking up, right?
他枪我下来。
He may gun me down.
你在说什么，叔叔？ 你疯了吗？
What are you saying, uncle? Are you mad?
他怎么能记住你的梦想吗？
How can he remember your dream?
他是新的，可能会得到混淆。
He's new, may have got confused.
我个人的生活是非常开心，因为ofyou的。
My personal life is very happy now because ofyou.
你的职业生涯，舅舅发生了什么事？
What happened to your professional life, uncle?
这是一场灾难！
lt's a total disaster!
兄弟在法律主导在家庭和博纳亚阿迪的主宰我在办公室。
Brother-in-law dominates in home and Adhi dominates me in office.
博纳亚阿迪带给我的记忆中，
Adhi brings to my memory,
明天的早餐，你的兄弟在法律已经邀请博纳亚阿迪的家庭。
your brother-in-law has invited Adhi's family for breakfast tomorrow.
他怎么能作出决定，我的梦想吗？
How can he take decisions in my dream?
这是我的梦想，对吧？
This is my dream, right?
他们采取的决定。 - 然后呢？
They're taking the decisions. - Then?
睡觉帕德玛纳巴SIMHA！
Sleeping Padmanabha Simha!
所有这些人物和场景都是从他的想法。
All these characters and scenes are from his thoughts.
得到它。
l got it.
他创造了这一幕像我与我的兄弟在法律上博纳亚阿迪。
He created this scene to take on Adhi like l did with my brother-in-law.
你这样做是正确的叔叔。
You got it right, uncle.
所以，你必须是一个在个人和职业生活！
So, you must be number one in personal and professional life too!
您必须是你的梦想世界的皇帝。
You must be the Emperor of your dream world.
这就是睡老人祝福！
That's what sleeping elderly man wishes!
我Baadshah的！ 一旦L决定战争变得一边倒！
l'm Baadshah! Once l decide war becomes one sided!
这是不喜欢吃早餐，但在星级酒店的自助餐。
This isn't like breakfast but buffet in star hotel.
如果这样，他吃我的儿子会成为像我一样。
lf he eats like this, my son would become like me.
什么？......
What?...
他已经开始了清晨！
He has started it early morning!
他要发飙了，直到结婚，L允许他。
He wanted to freak out till marriage, l permitted him to.
你是谁给我的权限吗？ 我的脚，该死的！
Who are you to give me permissions? My foot, damn it!
杉杉的时候，他喝醉了。
Firs time, he got drunk.
第一次吗？ 我一直在喝20年的白天和黑夜，
First time? l've been drinking day and night of 20 years,
你知道我的脚！
you know my foot!
你为什么老盯着我？
Why are you staring at me?
你想喝点什么？ lfyou想要拥有它。
Do you want to drink? lfyou want, have it.
无需害怕任何一个傻瓜！
No need to fear any fool!
什么？
What?
他听你，请管好他。 - 我会照顾他。
He listens to you, please manage him. - l'll take care of him.
大师，他的感觉不好，请进来。
Guru, he's feeling bad, please come.
如果升去，如果他觉得呢？ - 为我的缘故。
Should l go if he feels? - For my sake.
L'要走了，因为我的灵魂伴侣，希望它。 - 对不起，妹夫。
l'm leaving because my soul mate wants it. - Sorry, brother-in-law.
得到了信息，苦行僧BHAI的男人已经进入了城市。
Got info that Sadhu bhai's men have entered the city.
lntelligence报告说，他们正在规划的东西在这里。
lntelligence reports say they're planning something here.
他们可能做的一切，Baadshah将在他们身后！
Whatever they may do, Baadshah will be behind them!
Baadshah现在就在你面前！
Baadshah is right before you now!
Baadshah是在你的眼前。
Baadshah is right before your eyes.
他Baadshah！
He's Baadshah!
我Baadshah的！
l'm Baadshah!
LF Baadshah决定战争将成为一个片面的。
lf Baadshah decides war will become one sided.
你会消失得无影无踪。
You'll vanish without a trace.
不要把他当回事。 专注于苦行僧的人。
Don't take him seriously. Focus on Sadhu's men.
此后l和我的团队会就可以了。
Hereafter l and my team will be on it.
你是你的Dhoni团队！
You're a Dhoni and you've a team too!
苦行僧的人不超过30分钟的城市。
Sadhu's men are not in city for more than 30 minutes.
警方已经了解它。 告诉他们要保持高度警惕。
Already police know about it. Tell them to be on high alert.
我询问后，你告诉我，
l've inquired after you told me,
苦行僧的男子疯狂的罗伯特和洛基拉苏尔是在城市郊区的狗屋。
Sadhu's men Crazy Robert and Rocky Rasool are in Dog House on city outskirts.
为什么你是沉闷的，爸爸？
Why are you dull, dad?
升rememberyour妈妈看到海得拉巴。
l rememberyour mother on seeing Hyderabad.
升与你和你的母亲住在一个小房子。
l used to live in a small house with you and your mother.
我以为金钱就是一切生命。
l thought money is everything to life.
母亲给了比金钱的关系的重要性。
Mother gave importance to relationships than money.
我不明白。
l couldn't understand it then.
我对不起fatherfor不会告诉你母亲还活着。
l'm sorry fatherfor not telling you that mother is alive.
我实现我的目标，在不久的将来，你与母亲和团结。
l'll achieve my aim in near future and unite you with mother.
按满足？ 为什么呢？
Press meet? Why?
问我为什么？ 人们不应该知道关于你的才华吗？
Asking me why? Shouldn't people know about your talent?
只有那么睡觉的帕德玛纳巴SIMHA会得到满意的，对不对？
Only then sleeping Padmanabha Simha would get satisfied, right?
是的，叔叔。
Yes, uncle.
最新新闻，令人震惊的新闻部门，
Breaking news to you, shocking news to department,
惊天新闻黑手党！
shaking news to mafia!
我会赶上苦行僧的男人谁进入了城市在一天之内！
l'll catch Sadhu's men who entered the city in one day!
lfthey听我的，我会逮捕他们如果不L'LL枪，他们下来！
lfthey listen to me, l'll arrest them if not l'll gun them down!
升容忍他到现在我的妹妹。
l tolerated him till now for my sister.
l必须立即暂停他。
l must suspend him immediately.
警方的信息，我们必须没有任何进一步的拖延。
Police have the information, we mustn't delay any further.
材料必须在今晚出动。
Material must be dispatched tonight.
在这种苦行僧的任何延迟不会很容易。
Any delay in this Sadhu won't take it easy.
串行炸弹必须摇滚随着海得拉巴，新德里，孟买，加尔各答。
Serial bombs must rock Delhi, Mumbai, Kolkata along with Hyderabad.
这必须是明天此时在印度各地新闻。
This must be the breaking news all over lndia by tomorrow at this time.
你是谁？
Who are you?
Kondaveeti SIMHA许多罪犯在Kondaveedu裤子湿。
Kondaveeti Simha who made many criminals to wet pants in Kondaveedu.
的Bobbili SIMHA处罚掠夺者在Pasupathy在公共。
Bobbili Simha who punished plunderer Pasupathy in public.
谁救Samarasimha RAYALASEEMA的魔掌ofVeeraraghava派。
Samarasimha who saved Rayalaseema from the clutches ofVeeraraghava's faction.
Lakshminarasimha谁创造的恐惧症等小人Dharmabhiksham。
Lakshminarasimha who created fear psychosis in villain Dharmabhiksham.
SIMHA谁救胜利城Veerakesava的人。
Simha who saved people of Vijayanagar from Veerakesava.
帕德玛纳巴SIMHA的是混合放在一起Simhas。
Padmanabha Simha is a mix of all the Simhas put together.
与大肚腩，你看像猪一样均匀。
With that pot belly you look like a pig in uniform.
你可以做什么是地狱的人吗？
What the hell can you do man?
你为什么要戴口罩？ 灰尘过敏？
Why are you wearing mask? Dust allergy?
如果我没有叔叔焦点，你会不会获得名声。
No uncle if l'm in focus, you'll not get fame.
你坐在车里。 我会完成他们到您的帐户和信用卡。
You sit in the car. l'll finish them and credit it to your account.
许多无辜的人会模具ifthese炸弹熄灭。
many innocents would die ifthese bombs go off.
您必须阻止它不惜任何代价。
You must stop it at any cost.
杀了他！
Kill him!
告诉我，拉姆！
Tell me, Ram!
我已经恢复了RDX。
l've recovered the RDX.
由于他们的计划已经失败，苦行僧BHAI将来到海得拉巴。
Since their plan has failed, Sadhu bhai will come to Hyderabad.
我们正在接近目标。
We're nearing the target.
DCP帕德玛纳巴SIMHA已经失去了平衡，因为专业的故障。
DCP Padmanabha Simha has lost balance because of professional failures.
因此，他追赶未知苦行僧BHAI的男子作了发言。
So he made statements of catching unknown Sadhu bhai's men.
他的代表，我们深表歉意。
We apologise on his behalf.
我们已经决定从今天起暂停他...
We've decided to suspend him from today...
这尸体是洛基拉苏尔！ 苦行僧BHAI的男人！
That dead body is Rocky Rasool! Sadhu bhai's man!
男孩，只有驴等待订单，狮子等情况。
Boy, only donkeys wait for orders, lion waits for situation.
我一个警察的事迹不止是字。
l'm a police of deeds notjust words.
我会做我说，我会说我做的。
l'll do what l say and l'll say what l do.
苦行僧BHAI！ 巨蟹座和ALD的可能治愈。
Sadhu Bhai! Cancer and AlDS may have cure.
但如果你对我...
But ifyou take on me...
你是耸人听闻，大爷！
You were sensational, uncle!
你的表现粉碎了你哥哥AW和博纳亚阿迪了惊讶。
Your performance shattered your brother-in-aw and Adhi got astonished.
升现在迫切需要一个女孩。 - 这是什么肮脏的愿望，叔叔？
l need a girl urgently now. - What's this dirty wish, uncle?
什么这么脏吗？
What's so dirty in it?
英雄有一个项目吵架后的场景在电影歌曲。
Heroes have an item song after a fight scene in films.
我想一个项目女孩。 - 女LTEM？
l want an item girl. - ltem girl?
我不希望任何项目的女孩，无论是ANUSHKA或塔曼纳
l don't want any item girl, either Anushka or Tamanna,
我不介意也都。
l don't mind both also.
它的不可能的，叔叔。 - 为什么不呢？
lt's not possible, uncle. - Why not?
为什么限制在梦中？ LS梦想没有？
Why restrictions in dream? ls it dream or not?
这是梦想，我们不是决策者。 - 那么，谁决定？
This is dream, we're not the deciders. - Then, who decides?
睡觉帕德玛纳巴SIMHA！
Sleeping Padmanabha Simha!
任何幻想的女孩，他会招待你。
Any girl he imagines would entertain you.
lsn't呢？ - 是的，叔叔。
lsn't it? - Yes, uncle.
谁是他的选择吗？
Who is his choice?
我的的纱丽是绿色信号...
My sari is green signal to you...
我已经给你带来的甜蜜...
l've brought you the sweet...
你闷热烈日...
You're sultry hot Sun...
我一盆冷水......
l'm a pot of chilled water...
哦，我的上帝！
Oh my God!
告诉我，她的房子在哪里？
Show me, where's her house?
愿她的羞涩见鬼去吧...
May her shyness go to hell...
她伤了我的心，成片......
She broke my heart into pieces...
告诉我，你想要什么？ 高级或山谷下来......
Tell me what do you want? Higher up or valley down...
欢迎，我的名字是Kanakam ...
Welcome, my name is Kanakam...
走进我的梦想，但没有人可以让我们...
Come into my dreams but nobody can get us...
LT的正常年轻有梦遗...
lt's normal for young to have wet dreams...
如果它不是酒足饭饱后，所有的夜晚是地狱......
lf it is not satiated, it's hell all the night...
通宵升这样做...
All night l did that...
你看起来很可爱的我...
You look very cute to me...
lfyou希望你的愿望是什么，你已经花了很多...
lfyou want what you desire, you've to spend a lot for it...
有一个捷径，不花一分钱......
There's a short cut to have it without spending a penny...
下获取的封面... 闭上你的眼睛......
Get under the covers... close your eyes...
跳转梦想的行列...... 那里有一个爆炸...
Jump the bandwagon of dreams... have a blast there...
说得好，我亲爱的人......
Well said, my dear man...
每天追，试图打动...... 你为什么要撕？
Chase every day, try to impress... why do you want to rip it?
不会浪费你的时间吗？ 你会不会结束，血压高吗？
Won't your time get wasted? Won't you end with high BP?
我一个大号新书细胞... 让它成为任何人...
l'm a queen ofyour cell... let it be anyone...
进入梦想与快照的手指...
Get into the dreams with the snap of a finger...
它的幸福的天堂在街道的欲望...
lt's bliss of heaven in the streets of desire...
他是警方的线人谁发个计划惨遭失败。
He's the police informer who made months of plan to fail miserably.
小费你死之前，我会做，我计划做。
A tip before you die, l'll do what l planned to do.
有没有人来阻止我。
There's no one to stop me.
还有一个人！
There's one man!
他是谁？
Who is he?
我抓住它提到Baadshah的名字，在你的眼中看到恐惧，
l got it on seeing fear in your eyes at the mention of Baadshah's name,
你一定会死在手中Baadshah。
you'd surely die in the hands of Baadshah.
你死之前，一个令人震惊的信息。
A shocking information before you die.
Baadshah太相同的人员l工作。
Baadshah too works for the same officer l work for.
该人员是谁？
Who is that officer?
Baadshah警方工作。
Baadshah is working for police.
BHAI，L现在的理解是他打我的方式。
Bhai, l understood it now by the way he hit me.
蒙面男子Baadshah！
The masked man was Baadshah!
是的，帕德玛纳巴SIMHA是一个小丑。
Yes, Padmanabha Simha is a buffoon.
他甚至没有赶上一挑口袋，直到日期。
He didn't even catch a pick-pocket till date.
升既要Baadshah，背后的他和警察背后Baadshah的！
l want both Baadshah behind him and the police officer behind Baadshah!
随着婚姻时间的临近，我的感觉就像一个网球球冲我来了！
As marriage time approaches, l feel like a tennis ball coming at me!
不要担心，让它成为任何问题，我会踢足球。
Don't worry, let it be any problem, l'll play football with it.
请合作从容！
Please co-operate calmly!
You'rejust一个婚礼策划师，你怎么敢触碰新娘！
You'rejust a wedding planner, how dare you touch the bride!
范围，而这种变化是什么？
What's your range and this change?
我们不知道您的种姓或过去！
We don't know your caste or past!
这个讨厌的东西是什么？
What's this nasty things?
你为什么问我这个问题？ - 谁应该问，然后呢？
Why are you asking me that? - Who should l ask then?
睡觉帕德玛纳巴SIMHA！
Sleeping Padmanabha Simha!
我已经告诉过你很多次，所有这些人物和场景都是他的梦想。
l've told you many times all these characters and scenes are his dreams.
为什么你总是问我同样的问题吗？
Why do you always ask me the same question?
我抓住它，第一次，对不对？ 升弄糊涂了。
l got it, first time, right? l got confused.
他为什么会得到如此糟糕的想法？
Why is he getting such lousy thoughts?
不知道是什么，他正计划与此！
Don't know what he is planning with this!
没关系，萨拉萨会不记得这一切，对不对？
That's okay, Janaki won't remember all this, right?
她怎么能记住你的梦想吗？ 你说话像个疯子一样。
How can she remember your dream? You speak like a mad man.
不要生气，帕德玛的计划是太混乱了！
Don't get angry, Padma's schemes are too confusing!
他们杀了举报人凯萨瓦。
They've killed our informer Kesava.
我肯定苦行僧BHAI是在城市。
l'm sure Sadhu Bhai is in city.
你要小心。
You be careful.
没有人必须知道你Baadshah的，直到任务完成。
Nobody must know you're Baadshah till the mission is accomplished.
我的母亲太不知道我Baadshah的！
My mother too doesn't know l'm Baadshah!
你Baadshah吗？
Are you Baadshah?
刑事整个警察部门后？
Are the criminal entire police department is after?
否，请听我说，妈妈。 - 什么？
No, please listen to me, mother. - What no?
我的担心已经成真！ 你像你父亲toojust的...
My fears have come true! You toojust like yourfather...
永远不会再显示你的脸，我的生活中。
Never again show your face to me in life.
母亲，成为Baadshah升的原因是Siddhu！
Mother, the reason l became Baadshah is Siddhu!
他为什么没有来呢，妈妈呢？ - 他会来的。
Why hasn't he come yet, mother? - He'll come.
你知道我是今天去美国，
You know l'm going to US today,
希望一起吃早餐，你为什么这么晚才回来？
wished to have breakfast together, why did you come so late?
如果他来得晚，会有一个原因。
lf he comes late, there will be a reason.
你说，不管他做什么是正确的。
You say whatever he does is right.
它需要时间来得到这个印。
lt took time to get this printed.
每天当你的咖啡，你必须记住，妈妈和我。
Every day when you've coffee, you must remember mom and me.
同样，我们也应该想想你在喝咖啡的同时。
Likewise we too should think about you while having coffee.
你看到了吗？
Did you see?
傻了！ 给我你的手！
Silly! Give me your hand!
他会记得我现在的每一秒。 是怎么回事？
He'll remember me every second now. How is it?
您应该永远是这样。
You both should always be like this.
l也将但我怀疑他。 - 疑古我？
l will but l doubt him. - Doubting me?
你通过civils，你为什么要去美国，而不是参加面试吗？
You passed civils, why are you going to US instead of attending interview?
l可有什么LAS和LPS人员在这里赚取。
l can more there what lAS and lPS officers earn here.
人们认为这样的，这就是为什么顶去那里和废料仍然在这里。
People think like this, that's why top goes there and scrap remains here.
孟买在哪里？ lsn't在印度？
Where's Bombay? lsn't it in lndia?
你有一个很好的工作机会，你为什么不走呢？
You got a good job offer there, why didn't you go?
您可能已经走了，儿子。
You could've gone there, son.
母亲，他是你出生以来。 升加入你要晚得多。
Mother, he was with you since birth. l joined you much later.
你找到了我在街上和比他亲切地把我养大，
You found me on streets and raised me affectionately than him,
怎么能忘了吗，妈妈？
how can l forget that, mother?
lfyou再次谈论它，我会杀了你。
lfyou talk about it again, l'll kill you.
看妈妈，他疏远himselffrom的我。
Look mom, he's distancing himselffrom me.
对不起，我不能再说了。 - 第..
Sorry, l'll never say that again. - No...
我说对不起，对不对？
l said sorry, right?
他脾气坏，母亲。 - 然后呢？
He's short tempered, mother. - Then what?
升忘记了我的包，我会得到它，母亲。
l forgot my bag, l'll get it, mother.
要小心，儿子。 - 好吧，妈妈。
Be careful, son. - Okay, mother.
天色渐晚，来的太快，！
Getting late, come fast!
不......不......我害怕...... 我只是看！ - 光了！
No...no...l'm scared... l'll just watch!- Light it!
我们的调查证明，背后的高尔杉聊天爆炸苦行僧BHAI是。
Our investigations prove Sadhu Bhai is behind the Gulshan Chat blasts.
我们已经惊动队，
We've alerted the teams,
我们正在采取一切预防措施，以避免此类事件的发生。
we're taking all precautions to avoid such incidents from happening.
我会确保政府。 补偿的家庭ofvictims在爆炸。
l'll ensure Govt. compensates to the families ofvictims in the blast.
你看到这样的新闻吗？
Did you see this news?
在孟买当地的火车发生炸弹爆炸事件。 许多无辜的人死亡。
Bomb blast in Bombay local train. Many innocent people died.
LT常见印度。
lt's common in lndia.
如果l已在爆炸中死亡，你会这样反应？
Would you react like this if l had died in the blast?
电源或贫穷不是最大的威胁，
Power or poverty isn't the biggest threat,
恐怖分子和黑手党是我们最大的威胁。
terrorists and mafia are the biggest threat to us.
他们必须被无情地拍摄。
They must be shot ruthlessly.
我不希望成为一名警察赚钱orfor的电源，
l don't want to be a police officer to make money orfor power,
为了我的国家，
for the sake of my country,
清理苦行僧BHAI和他的团伙杀害许多无辜的印第安人，
to clean up Sadhu bhai and his gang for killing many innocent lndians,
升拿下90％与目标Civils，
l scored 90% in Civils with that aim,
我已经清除了95％的电源，
l've cleared mains with 95% ,
选择我了高年级每的事件OFTHE培训期间，
l got selected with high grades in every event ofthe training period,
你为什么拒绝我呢？
why did you reject me then?
你父亲Dhanraj的原因是为您的拒绝。
Your father Dhanraj is the reason for your rejection.
我父亲20年前去世的原因？
How can my father be the reason who died 20 years ago?
你的父亲仍然活着。
Your father is still alive.
你想杀死苦行僧BHAI的，
You want to kill Sadhu Bhai,
你的父亲经营澳门娱乐场下相同的苦行僧BHAI工作。
your father runs a casino in Macau working under the same Sadhu Bhai.
我们不能招收考生刑事家族史。
We mustn't recruit candidates criminal family history.
L'一直试图赶上苦行僧BHAI，20年，
l've been trying to catch Sadhu Bhai for 20 years,
Dhanraj你父亲是一个金融专家，
yourfather Dhanraj is a financial expert,
没有得到认可，他的天赋感到沮丧，
getting frustrated for not getting recognition for his talent,
他加入了苦行僧作为其财务顾问。
he joined Sadhu as his financial advisor.
苦行僧离开印度时，你父亲绑你和motherwith他。
When Sadhu left lndia, yourfather tied to take you and motherwith him.
你的母亲没有同意。
Your mother didn't agree.
她使他相信，你和她已经在事故中死亡。
She made him believe that you and she had died in an accident.
同样，她对你撒谎，你父亲是死了。
Likewise she lied to you that your father is dead.
看到希望看到火在你的眼睛和诚实，你的话。
l saw hope seeing fire in your eyes and honesty in your words.
lnfiltrate帮你父亲的帮助下，
lnfiltrate the gang with your father's help,
lntelligence报告说苦行僧，在印度正在筹划重大爆炸，
lntelligence reports say Sadhu is planning major blasts in lndia,
我们必须不惜任何代价阻止他，
we must stop him at any cost,
如果你们做的为L说，我会放弃所有指控你父亲。
ifyou do as l say, l'll drop all the charges against yourfather.
苦行僧BHAI是从现在开始我的目标。
Sadhu bhai is my target from now.
这样的操作Baadshah开始。
Operation Baadshah began like that.
他抹去了许多与他的叔叔的帮助下，加入该团伙的歹徒。
He erased many gangsters joining the gang with the help of his uncle.
他停了下来苦行僧BHAI，救了我们从一个大的灾难。
He stopped Sadhu bhai and saved us from a big disaster.
他改革了他的父亲和他远离黑手党断奶。
He reformed his father and weaned him away from mafia.
对不起儿子，升误解你。
Sorry son, l misunderstood you.
父亲总是谈论你！
Father always talks about you!
的父母亲在哪里？
Where's yourfather?
如果孩子做的错误，父母纠正他们，
lf children do mistakes, parents correct them,
但犯的错误，你纠正我。
but l committed the mistake and you corrected me.
我生下这样一个好儿子感到自豪！
l'm proud of giving birth to such a good son!
升ltaly发生了什么事感到羞耻。
l feel shame for what had happened in ltaly.
升无聊你不知道你，我的球理念。
Without knowing about you, l bored you with my ball philosophy.
像主奎师那你跑展会，但叫你为弟子和继承人。
You ran the show like Lord Krishna but l called you as disciple and heir.
没问题，最后你叫我为情人，对吧？
No problem, finally you called me as lover, right?
接下来，你会说老公！ - 这是不那么容易。
Next you'd say husband! - lt isn't that easy.
我的父亲一定知道博纳亚阿迪是一个叛徒。
My father must know Adhi is a traitor.
他必须说服并取消婚姻。 你能怎么办呢？
He must get convinced and cancel the marriage. How can you do it?
我已经安排的歌曲，舞蹈和明天的sangeeth运动。
l've arranged the song, dance and movements for tomorrow's sangeeth.
Sangeeth Pilli的家庭！
Sangeeth of Pilli family!
Pilli家族Sangeeth必须通话oftown，
Sangeeth of Pilli family must be talk oftown,
一切都是完美的，对不对？ - 规划是完美的，先生。
everything is perfect, right? - Planning is perfect sir.
lfyou不希望任何剧透，保持帕德玛纳巴SIMHA的远离饮料，
lfyou don't want any spoilers, keep Padmanabha Simha away from drinks,
你请求他个人。
you request him personally.
去......去......
Go...go...
姐夫，你是著名的儿童。
Brother-in-law, you're famous with children too.
名人堂取决于你做的工作。
Fame depends on the work you do.
你说得对，妹夫。
You're right, brother-in-law.
L'VE小的要求。 - 那是什么？
l've a small request. - What's that?
我不想Pilli家族成为笑柄OFTHE镇，。
l don't want Pilli family to become laughing stock ofthe town.
所以，请不要今天喝。
So, please don't drink today.
如果升不抽烟你傻家人？
Should l not drink for your silly family?
叔叔，老人的请求，请放弃forjust一天。
Uncle, elderly man is requesting, please give up forjust a day.
升同意，因为我的灵魂伴侣的请求。
l agree because of my soul mate's request.
大哥！
Brother!
为什么是你哥哥吗？
Why is your brother here?
这是... - 谁邀请他？
That is... - Who invited him?
升邀请他，先生。 - 你呢？
l invited him, sir. - You?
他是不是相对的，他是一个敌人。 你知道吗？
He's not a relative, he's an enemy. Do you know that?
不要生气，先生？ 我知道你的战斗。
Don't get angry, sir? l know about your fight.
惩治这类家伙是不是让他们离开。
Punishment for such guys isn't keeping them away.
然后呢？ - 我们必须表现出他，他缺少什么！
Then?- We must show him what he's missing!
他必须看到Pilli家族的庄严和燃烧着嫉妒！
He must see Pilli family's grandeur and burn with jealous!
你说得对！ 我没有这个想法。
You're right! l didn't get this idea.
你精细哥哥吗？ - 好吧，亲爱的。
Are you fine brother? - Fine, dear.
你罚款，嫂嫂？ - 我很好。
Are you fine, sister-in-law? - l'm fine.
你轻视我的家人拒绝了我的儿子，
You belittled my family rejected my son,
得到你的女儿嫁给她的爱人。
and got your daughter married to her lover.
这就是为什么你离我们住了2年。
That's why you stayed away from us for 2 years.
观看Pilli家族的婚礼的庄严。
Watch the grandeur of Pilli family's wedding.
大哥！ - 请让他坐在第一排。
Brother! - Please make him sit in the first row.
请进来，妹夫。
Please come, brother-in-law.
谢谢儿子！ 多年后，我满足我的兄弟。
Thanks son! l could meet my brother after years.
感谢萨拉萨不是我，她告诉了我一切。
Thank Janaki not me, she told me everything.
欢迎您，妹夫！
Welcome, brother-in-law!
Sangeeth盛大的婚姻一样！ - 难道你不想结婚，然后呢？
Sangeeth is grand like marriage! - Don't you want marriage then?
只是为了好玩！ l表示婚姻是乐趣！
Just for fun! l said marriage is fun!
Baadshah找到谁是背后帕德玛纳巴之前的婚姻已经结束。
Find Baadshah who is behind Padmanabha before marriage is over.
需要亲自和你谈谈。
l need to talk to you personally.
帕德玛纳巴几天的行为有一个显着的差异。
There's a marked difference in Padmanabha's behaviour for few days.
观察他。
l observed him.
有些家伙BAAD ... - Baadshah！
Some guy Baad... - Baadshah!
他说他手机上。 他经常与他接触。
He's talking to him on phone. He's in regular touch with him.
他遇见他在夜幕的掩护下。 - 你有没有看到Baadshah？
He meets him under the cover of darkness. - Did you see Baadshah?
我尝试，但不能清楚地看到他的脸在黑暗中。
l did try but couldn't see his face clearly in dark.
但有一件事是肯定的，他是太危险的人。
But one thing is sure, he's too dangerous man.
你会为此感到震惊。 - 什么？
You'd be shocked for this. - What?
它似乎他会杀了你还。
lt seems he'll kill you also.
有些家伙Siddhu ... - 苦行僧BHAI！
Some guy Siddhu... - Sadhu Bhai!
这家伙！ 看来你和他一起工作，对吗？
That's the guy! lt seems you work with him, right?
你为什么要告诉我们？
Why are you telling this to us?
在婚姻中，我们都能得到什么？ 升期待你的东西，先生。
What do we get in the marriage? l expect something from you, sir.
不要告诉给任何人。
Don't tell about this to anyone.
我能建议你随着信息？ 这是免费的。
Can l advice you along with information? This is free.
告诉我。
Tell me.
lfyou矮个子?饮料，他会咳嗽关于Baadshah！
lfyou get the short man o drink, he'll cough up about Baadshah!
饮品在这里......？ - 这也是免费的。
Drinks here...? - This is also free.
什么？ - 一种特殊的一瓶适合你。
What? - A special bottle for you.
我已经答应了我的灵魂伴侣，今天不喝酒。
l've promised my soul mate not to drink today.
右，但新郎希望你喝酒。
Right but groom wants you to drink.
有一些果汁。 - 果汁是我没关系。
Have some juice. - Juice is okay to me.
他为什么改变路线，叫我叔叔？
Why has he changed route and calling me uncle?
不知道睡帕德玛纳巴SIMHA的有什么计划？
Don't know what's the plan of sleeping Padmanabha Simha?
你说得对！
You're right!
叔叔，果汁。
Uncle, juice.
为什么两杯？ “ - 喜欢它lfyou，你可以拥有它。
Why two glasses? - lfyou like it, you can have it.
喜欢它，叔叔？ - 神奇！ - 有一个太。
Liked it, uncle?- Fantastic! - Have that one too.
我能得到两个吗？ - 获取它。
Can l get two more? - Get it.
你有没有看到，拉玛？
Did you see, Rama?
缺少果汁。
Juice is missing.
谁喝了？
Who drank it?
客人抵达，启动程序 - 好先生。
Guests have arrived, start the program.- Okay sir.
妇女在家庭中实行2天的舞蹈，让我们开始与他们。
Women in the family practiced dance for 2 days, let's start with them.
跳舞？ 他们甚至不能正常做饭。
Dance? They can't even cook properly.
他们会过于跳舞吗？ 客人可以扔了。
Would they dance too? Guests may throw up.
任何功能将开始与我的家人我的行为！
Any function in my family would start with my act!
冰雹湿婆帕尔瓦蒂！
Hail Lord Shiva and Parvathi!
舞蹈和节奏合拍是幸福...
Dance and rhythm in tune is bliss...
代理和Ovation是天上...
Acting and ovation is heavenly...
LN行动的姿势...
ln action...in pose...
那是什么舞？ - Bharathanatyam！
What's that dance? - Bharathanatyam!
不，这是愚蠢的舞蹈！
No, it's silly dance!
就像走在雪水什么运动？
What's that movement like walking in slush?
那是什么烂脸上的表情吗？
What's that lousy expression on face?
你停下来！
You stop it!
Kamalahasan禁止'Vishwaroopam'哭了，
Kamalahasan cried for banning 'Vishwaroopam',
如果他看到这个舞蹈，他会死在震动。
if he sees this dance, he'll die in shock.
我们的舞蹈将让你扔了吗？
Will our dances make you throw up?
因此，他们有酒混合汁。
So they had the liquor mixed juice.
我们高级NTR球迷！
We're fans of senior NTR!
你想观看演出！
You wanna watch the show!
父母把我家...
Parents' threw me out of home...
丈夫太甩了我......
Husband too dumped me...
我所有ofjust 16，如果你结婚，这是仅有3海里......
l'm all ofjust sixteen, ifyou marry, it's just 3 knots...
升去Gudiwada的...
l went to Gudiwada...
升去贡土尔...
l went to Guntur...
Eluru ...内洛尔... 升去了很多地方......
Eluru...Nellore... l went to many places...
无论升......无论我... 他们要求更多...
Wherever l go...whatever l do... they ask for more...
血淋淋的流氓前来观看演出的人...
Bloody rogues who come to watch the show...
愿你的家变成黄金...
May your home turn into gold...
愿我的身体变成美丽的...
May my body turn beautiful...
你高，你想我tojoin？
You're on high, would you like tojoin me?
将你的激情头上？
Will you take on the passion head on?
有一间小屋...
There's a hut...
有一个婴儿床...
There's a cot...
必胜客和婴儿床都是空的，没有一个人...
Hut and cot both are empty without a man...
女孩高，夜晚凉爽的说还好...
The girl is on high and the cool night says okay...
我的青春是华阳...
My youth is foryou...
LT的全力以赴为您...
lt's going all out for you...
为了解渴欲望...
To quench desires...
喝醉了和舞蹈你不感到羞耻吗？
Aren't you ashamed to get drunk and dance?
你毁了Pilli家族的荣誉。 你为什么alsojoin呢？
You ruined Pilli family honour. Why did you alsojoin them?
他们希望我tojoin ... - 你会，加入ifthey问？
They wanted me tojoin... - Will you join ifthey ask?
他们是毫无意义的... - 这不是他们的错先生。
They're senseless... - lt's not their mistake sir.
你是谁，告诉我吗？ - 你的女婿加入白酒tojuice。
Who are you to tell me that? - Your son-in-law added liquor tojuice.
观看此视频，先生。
Watch this video, sir.
矮个告诉约Baadshah？
Did that short man tell about Baadshah?
他说什么？ 他杀了我thatjuice的。
What will he say? He's killing me for thatjuice.
这样，如果我们不使用绑架帕德玛纳巴从这里开始，
No use like this, ifwe kidnap Padmanabha from here,
我们的问题会得到解决。
our problem would get solved.
你怎么敢！ 你会试图绑架我？ - 别喊！
How dare! Will you try to kidnap me? - Don't shout!
凭借专业的嫉妒比你变得更出名，
With professional jealousy of becoming more famous than you,
你会弯腰，以如此之低的水平？
would you stoop down to so low level?
别喊，我会扼杀你的脖子。
Don't shout, l'll strangle your neck.
你会杀了我吗？ 杀了我！
Will you kill me? Kill me!
我理解你和你的性格。
l've understood you and your character.
你加入白酒tojuice和现在打我的妹夫。
You added liquor tojuice and now beat my brother-in-law.
你是人类还是野兽？
Are you human or beast?
你为什么喊女婿？ 以轻松有趣，算了吧。
Why are you shouting at son-in-law? Take it easy as fun and forget it.
这不好玩，他击败了我的姐夫！
lt's not fun, he beat my brother-in-law!
女婿本家族！
Son-in-law ofthis family!
多少钱我姐夫对我的感觉吗？ 我希望这个梦是真实的！
How much my brother-in-law is feeling for me? l hope this dream is true!
倒在他的脚下，并寻求他的宽恕。
Fall at his feet and seek his forgiveness.
你在想什么？ 秋季，如果不结婚，可能会取消。
What are you thinking? Fall, if not marriage may get cancelled.
他为什么要呢？
Why should he?
专员必须属于滥用他在他的脚下。
Commissioner must fall at his feet for abusing him.
我们也有家族的荣誉。
We too have family honour.
荣誉？ 你的儿子犯了一个错误，
Honour? Your son made a mistake,
而不是责骂他，你支持他。
instead of chiding him, you're supporting him.
没有使用越来越像公牛，增长你的大脑。
No use is growing like a bull, grow your brain.
你怎么敢用手指指向我！
How dare you point finger at me!
lfyou留在这儿，我有你扔出去。
lfyou stay here, l'll have you thrown out.
我们不是妇女要等到扔出去。
We're not women to wait till thrown out.
我们会粉碎你的脸！
We'll smash your faces!
这个讨厌的是什么？ 取消婚姻，这是结束。
What's this nasty? cancel marriage, that's the end.
lfyou的斗争中，它会创建为你的坏形象。
lfyou fight, it'll create bad image for you.
取消这门亲事！
This marriage is cancelled!
谁是你说的吗？ L'告诉现在！
Who are you to say that? l'm telling now!
这段婚姻被取消。
This marriage is cancelled.
滚出去！ - 让我们去，儿子。 血腥的建议！
Get out! - Let's go, son. Bloody proposal!
血腥？ 你是一个血淋淋的家庭。
Bloody? You're a bloody family.
闭上你的采空区！ - 冷静下来，先生。
Shut your gob! - Calm down sir.
婚姻的取消不会丢失你的家族荣誉。
Your family honour isn't lost by the cancellation of marriage.
这注定了一个更好的女婿加入家族。
lt's destined that a better son-in-law would join the family.
这就是为什么发生这种情况，你说什么？“ - 是的，先生。
That's why this happened, what do you say?- Yes sir.
那家伙是不是装修成萨拉萨夫人的框架。
That guy wasn't fitting into the frame with Janaki madam.
新郎丰富多彩的帧必须改变！
Groom must change for colourful frame!
颜色......无数的颜色...
Colours...myriad of colours...
我想看到的颜色的脸颊OFTHE美容...
l want to see the colours on cheeks ofthe beauty...
必须穿丝绸纱丽...
Must wear a silk sari...
套用一个点...
Apply a dot...
婚姻乐队必须发挥... 与她喜结良缘......
Marriage band must play on... Tie the knot with her...
她让我的生活在树冠下的合作伙伴...
Make her my life partner under the canopy...
虎虎.??.. 来，虎...
Tiger...tiger... come, Tiger...
你的祭坛上牺牲我的美丽...
My beauty is sacrificed on your altar...
我美丽的花蕾...
My beautiful bud...
这心脏雨ofjasmine ...
lt's a rain ofjasmine in heart...
我异国情调的芒果Chittoor ...
Get me the exotic mangoes of Chittoor...
我孕吐的味道..
Show me the taste of morning sickness..
L合租可爱的拥抱... 5升你的魅力...
May l share lovely hugs... May l charm you...
LN高点和低点，炸毁大脑用我的魔力...
ln highs and lows, blow up brain with my magic...
l对象，如果你做任何事情我吗？
Would l object ifyou do anything with me?
它可能是孕吐或者什么，我的美丽，是你的心脏......
lt may be morning sickness or anything, my beauty and heart is yours...
可能蔓延幸福的床...
May spread the bed of happiness...
凯萨瓦部门牺牲了自己的生命，
Kesava sacrificed his life for the department,
这是我们的责任，站在他的家人。
it's our duty to stand by his family.
拿去吧，亲爱的。
Take it, dear.
我们必须感谢你的父亲。
We must thank your father.
lfyou需要任何帮助，请给我打电话。
lfyou need any help, please call me.
升了12个国家的警察，你跟我玩，
l played with police of 12 countries, you played with me,
没有我知道博纳亚阿迪的手过RDX部门，
l know Adhi didn't hand over RDX to the department,
我知道Baadshah是在你身后，
l know Baadshah is behind you,
告诉我，Baadshah？
tell me, where's Baadshah?
如果没有你会死的。
lf not you will die.
叛徒喜欢他背叛的钱，
Traitors like him betray for money,
但很多警察宁愿牺牲生命的责任。
but many police officers would sacrifice life for duty.
升应该发动你的电影吗？
Should l launch your film?
升在电视上看到你的英勇，并认为这将有助于我的电影。
l saw your heroism on TV and thought it would help my film.
谁看到我吗？
Who would see me?
疯狂的罗伯特，他会尿床，如果他看到你与我。
Crazy Robert, he would wet the bed if he sees you with me.
如果没有？ - 他会杀了我。
lf not? - He would kill me.
你与他什么？ - 怨！
What's your connection with him? - Enmity!
他问钱，我说去地狱。
He asked money and l said go to hell.
他受伤和l得到黄牌警告。
He got hurt and l got booked.
在意大利，他对我做出了尝试。
He made an attempt on me in ltaly.
你为什么去ltaly用懒懒地面对？
Why did you go to ltaly with this idly face?
要查看位置。 但协调员戈皮骗了我。
To see locations. But coordinator Gopi cheated me.
好吧，再见。
Okay, bye.
为什么你看到吗？ 告诉我。
Why are you seeing there? Tell me.
他没有来送他的侄女。
He didn't come and sent his niece.
为什么你看到了吗？ 告诉我。
Why are you seeing there again? Tell me.
她带着两条尾巴。
She came with two tails.
拉闸限电等这些休息是什么？
What are these breaks like power cuts?
这是像我这样的创作者的问题，
That's the problem with creators like me,
当我们讲述什么，摆在我们面前的人物活灵活现，
when we narrate anything, characters come alive before us,
无法理解，如果它的梦想还是真实。
can't understand if it's dream or real.
毫无疑问！ 它是一个梦想！
No doubt! lt's a dream!
我想这是他的计划，我链接了一些女主角。
l think this is his plan to link me up with some heroine.
谁是女主角？
Who is the heroine?
我的英雄是力量星级！ - 我会冉冉升起的新星！
My hero is power star! - l'm rising star!
一起多的明星！ 的位置在哪里？
Together it's multi star! Where's the location?
告诉我，先生 - 阳光塞拉利昂把一些重量或没有？
Tell me sir.- Has Sunny Leone put on some weight or not?
为什么问前味吃吗？ 你要满足她，对吗？
Why ask about taste before eating? You going to meet her, right?
阳光塞拉利昂和l不要在这里看不到任何裙子。
He Sunny Leone and l don't see any skirt here.
博纳亚阿迪，他的父亲罗伯特疯狂... 他们为什么在这里？
Adhi, his father, Crazy Robert... why are they here?
我抓住它，这是高潮梦想。
l got it, this is climax to the dream.
他创造了这一幕，一起玩所有ofthem。
He has created this scene to play with all ofthem.
我们陷入这个烂摊子，因为新书响亮的嘴巴。
We got into this mess because ofyour loud mouth.
手在短期的人，让我们释放。
Hand over the short man to them and get us freed.
我们已经宣布了我的电影的发行日期。
We've announced the release date of my film.
把我交给他们吗？ 我在这里完成他们。
Hand me over to them? l'm here to finish them.
你们不觉得丢人参加与公牛的恶棍吗？
Aren't you ashamed to join villains with that bull?
不要喊了，哪来的Baadshah？
Stop shouting, where's Baadshah?
我在你面前，还在问Baadshah？
l'm before you, and still asking where's Baadshah?
我Baadshah的！ 如果Baadshah决定，战争会变成一边倒。
l'm Baadshah! lf Baadshah decides, war will turn one sided.
问他们，我们走吧。
Ask them, let's go.
我们必须看到的情绪和要求如果不是我们会得到敲击。
We must see the mood and ask if not we'll get rapped.
lsn't，苏里亚？ - 迷路！
lsn't it, Surya? - Get lost!
你竟敢打我！ 你怎么敢在我的世界我主宰！
How dare you beat me! How dare you dominate me in my world!
Yourworld？
Yourworld?
这是我的人的创造。
This is my man's creation.
什么废话？ 你清晨喝吗？
What's that nonsense? Did you drink early in the morning?
我胡说？
Am l talking nonsense?
所有ofyou是我的男人的创作。
All ofyou are my man's creations.
我的男人希望和决心让我接替他的睡觉。
My man wishes and is determined to make me succeed he's sleeping.
他在哪里睡觉？
Where's he sleeping?
你千万不要告诉他们你的梦想。 - 什么如果告诉？
You mustn't tell them you're in dream. - What if l tell?
你会死在梦中。
You'll die in dream.
我不能告诉你。
l'll not tell you.
住手！ l可不能告诉你！
Stop! l can't tell you!
l必须不能告诉你，如果L告诉我死。
l mustn't tell you, if l tell l'll die.
lfyou不告诉你肯定会死。 告诉我。
lfyou don't tell you'll surely die. Tell me.
为什么你像猪一样的滚动？ 你为什么不回答？
Why are you rolling like a pig? Why don't you answer us?
没想到竟然在梦中升升将受伤在梦中。
l didn't expect even in dream l would get hurt in dream.
他为什么会产生这种情况呢？
Why did he create such a situation?
没用的男人！ 我不希望任何保持原位垃圾桶梦。
Useless man! l don't want any ofthis trash dream.
l必须立即出来ofthis，。 但是，怎么样？
l must come out ofthis immediately. But how?
只要闭上你的眼睛，唱起来......起床了......我的王......
Just close your eyes and sing Get up...get up...my king...
你在想什么？
What are you thinking?
给我5分钟，我会告诉你一切。
Give me 5 minutes, l'll tell you everything.
起床起床...我的王......
Get up...get up...my king...
难道你不想起床吗？ 应叫你起床吗？
Don't you want to get up? Shall l wake you up?
你睡多久？ LS提出睡像日志？
How long will you sleep? ls it lodge to sleep like log?
而且该死的鼾声。 起床！
Moreover damn snores too. Get up!
起床！ - 起身！
Get up! - Got up!
为什么我仍然梦想？ 它意味着中国机失败。
Why am l still in dream? lt means China machine has failed.
所以，永远不要使用重复的中国机器。
So, never use duplicate Chinese machines.
你在看什么？ 起床！
What are you looking at? Get up!
拉玛饶预订我这个样子吗？ 拉玛饶是谁？
Did Rama Rao booked me like this? Who is Rama Rao?
我告诉他，先生。 我是要走过地狱。
l'll show him to you, sir. l'm going through hell.
就是他！
That's him!
他是婚礼策划师！
He's wedding planner!
他Baadshah！
He's Baadshah!
如果他Baadshah，他为什么像婚礼策划师？
lf he's Baadshah, why did he act like wedding planner?
你永远无法理解他的举动，
You can never understand his moves,
因为这是一个计划通过主记Baadshah！
because this is a plan by master mind Baadshah!
他附近博纳亚阿迪来萨拉萨的帮助下，
He came near Adhi with Janaki's help,
他用帕德玛纳巴SIMHA的梦想机，
he used Padmanabha Simha with dream machine,
他挑起把你带到印度。
he provoked and brought you to lndia.
喜欢使用诱饵猎虎，
Like using a bait to hunt tiger,
作为诱饵，Baadshah使用这个替罪羊。
Baadshah used this scapegoat as a bait.
这个梦想机将让我们的梦想成真梦想。
This dream machine will make our dreams come true in dream.
现在你的梦想，叔叔。 - 他怎么能决定我的梦想？
You're now in dream, uncle. - How can he decide my dream?
我们不是决策者。 睡觉帕德玛纳巴SIMHA！
We're not the deciders. Sleeping Padmanabha Simha!
您必须是皇帝新书的梦想。
You must be the emperor ofyour dream.
所以，这是不是一个梦。 - 这不是梦想，而是现实。
So, this is not a dream. - This is not dream but real.
他为什么选择我虽然在国内有这么多吗？
Why did he choose me though there are so many in home?
你看起来像纸巾，使用和扔掉！
You look like tissue paper, use and throw away!
这不是到这里来。
lt's not safe to be here.
拨打威尔逊和安排菜刀在Hakimpet空军基地。
Call Wilson and arrange for a chopper in Hakimpet airbase.
升招募他的一天，你回收的RDX发送给印度的！
l recruited him the day you recovered RDX sent to lndia!
这么多的变化，在一个字符。
So many variations in one character.
他跪不统一带来了整个黑手党。
He brought entire mafia to kneels without uniform.
现在，他是一个穿制服的人员。
Now he's an officer with uniform.
胆量lfyou've，试图逃离他。
lfyou've guts, try to escape from him.
没有警察可以让我20年来印度
No police officer could make me come to lndia for 20 years,
你让我来到这里，
you made me come here,
我会为您提供whateveryou问，做什么你问！
l'll offer you whateveryou ask and do whatever you ask!
离开我！
Leave me!
像他这样的二流子可能属于你俩的报价！
Loafers like him may fall foryour offers!
但L'VE这件衣服的地址。
But l've an address for this dress.
这个名字有一个历史！
There's a history to that name!
有没有人买NTR，将来也不会有任何人。
There wasn't anyone to buy NTR and there won't be anyone in future.
一个进步和LG就死了！
One step forward and lG will die!
你看到天蝎座炸毁了一步？
Did you see Scorpios blew up with one step?
你的一步，使电影触发器。
Your one step makes films to flop.
许多无辜的死在你所种植的炸弹。
Many innocents died in the bombs planted by you.
其中之一是升Siddhu爱那么多。
One among them is Siddhu l love so much.
L的决定的那一天，就杀了你。
l had decided that day to kill you.
我告诉你我完成它与你！
l told you l would finish it with you!
全部都不见了！ 只有我离开了。
All are gone! Only l'm left.
你被抓住了！
You got caught!
没有污染Pilli家庭，L'VE警务人员女婿。
Without polluting Pilli family, l've a police officer as son-in-law.
它的Pilli APPA饶祝福。
lt's Pilli Appa Rao's blessings.
当看到你快乐，
When l see you happy,
升觉得它就像一个教练看到他的学生打了六！
l feel it's like a coach seeing his student hit a six!
虽然这是例行的例子，它是新的！
Though it's routine example, it's new!
lsn't它像一个梦想，你叔叔？
lsn't it like a dream to you, uncle?
再做梦吗？
Dream again?
埔里 - DDR荣誉出品！
A PuLi - DDR Presentation